<?xml version="1.0" encoding="Windows-1252"?>
<CardDataCollection xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <CardData>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Liu Bei</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Hero Through Troubled Times

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Kindness:
During your main phase, you may give any number of cards from your hand to any number of heroes.
Once during your main phase, the first time you give out 2 or more cards to a target hero, you gain 1 health.

Rouse: (Emperor Ability)
Whenever you need to play or discard an ATTACK, you may ask each other SHU faction hero to play or discard an ATTACK for you, then its treated as you playing the ATTACK.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Liu Shan</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Emperor with No Achievements

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Relish:
Whenever you become the target of an ATTACK, ignore the effects of that ATTACK unless the attacker discards a basic card from their hand.

Devolution:
You may skip your main phase, then at the end of your turn, you may discard a card and target a hero. That hero immediately gains an extra turn after you end your turn.

Eiron: (Awakening Ability, Emperor Ability)
At the beginning of your turn, if you have the least amount of health among all heroes, you increase your max health by 1 unit, gain 1 health, and gain [ROUSE].

[Rouse]:
Whenever you need to play or discard an ATTACK, you may ask each other SHU faction hero to play or discard an ATTACK for you, then its treated as you playing the ATTACK.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Liu Zhang</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Patriotic Noble

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Do or Die:
During your main phase, you may play any card from your hand as a DUEL; after resolving the duel, both you and the loser of the duel draw a card. (You draw both cards if you were the loser of the duel.)
If you draw 2 or more cards via this effect during this phase, you lose the [DO OR DIE] ability until the end of turn.

Save the Emperor: (Emperor ability)
You may discard a card to use [ROUSE]. The target hero who used an ATTACK to respond to your [ROUSE] draws a card.

[Rouse]:
Whenever you need to play or discard an ATTACK, you may ask each other SHU faction hero to play or discard an ATTACK for you, then its treated as you playing the ATTACK.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Guan Yu</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Bearded Gentleman

Health/Gender:4M

Ability:

Saint Warrior:
You may play or discard any RED cards from your hand or equipment zone as an ATTACK.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhang Fei</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: A Match for Ten Thousand Warriors

Health/Gender:4M

Ability:

Roar:
You may play any number of ATTACK during your turn.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhuge Liang</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Prime Minister Who Has Passed His Prime

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Stargazing:
At the beginning of your turn, you may look at the top X cards of the library, where X is equal to the number of surviving heroes (Max 5); you may choose to put any number of these cards on top and bottom of the library in any order.

Empty Fort:
Whenever you have no cards in your hand, you cannot be the target of any ATTACK or DUEL.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhao Yun</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Young General

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Dragon Courage:
You may play or discard ATTACK cards as DODGE or vice versa.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Ma Chao</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Lone Horseman That Can Outmatch a Thousand Troops

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Horsemanship:
The physical range you see other heroes is reduced by 1.

Iron Calvary:
Whenever you play an ATTACK targeting a hero, you may perform a judgment. If the result is RED, the ATTACK cannot be cancelled by a DODGE.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Huang Yue Ying</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Veiled Heroine

Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Gathering Wisdom:
Whenever you play an non-delay tactics card, draw a card.

Wondrous Talent:
All tactics card you play may ignore any range requirements.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Huang Zhong</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Old But Strong

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Fearsome Archer:
Whenever you play an ATTACK, you may target a hero whose range between you and that hero is less than the rank of that ATTACK.

Whenever you target a hero with an ATTACK:
1. If the number of cards in that hero's hand is less than or equal to your's, this ATTACK cannot be cancelled by DODGE.
2. If the target hero's current health is greater than or equal to your health, this ATTACK deals 1 additional damage.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Wei Yan</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Bloodthirsty Lone Wolf

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Violent Spirit:
Whenever you deal damage to a player within your physical range, for each damage you have dealt, you may choose one:
1. You gain 1 health.
2. You draw 1 card.

(This effect still triggers if you end up damaging yourself. If you enter the Brink of Death state after taking damage, you must revive before this ability can be triggered.)

Surprise Tactics: (Limited Ability)
During your main phase, you may lose X life; then until the end of your turn, you may use additional X ATTACK cards and the physical range between you and other heroes is reduced by X.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Young Zhuge Liang</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Sleeping Dragon

Health/Gender: 3M

Eight Trigrams:
If you have no armor cards in your equipment zone, you are considered to have EIGHT TRIGRAMS equipped.
(Heroes with abilities that ignore armor may ignore this effect. The Eight Trigrams given by this ability cannot be discard by other effects.)

Arson:
During your main phase, you may play RED cards in your hand as BLAZE.

See Through:
You may play BLACK cards from your hand as IMPECCABLE PLAN.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhu Rong</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Queen of Wilds

Health/Gender: 4F

Ability:

Elephant Army:
You ignore the effects of BARBARIAN ASSAULT. Whenever a BARBARIAN ASSAULT is played by another hero, after it is resolved and put into graveyard, you may take the BARBARIAN ASSAULT card into your hand.

Fierce Edge:
Whenever you deal damage to a target hero, you may clash with that hero. If you win, you may take 1 card from that hero's hand or equipment zone into your hand.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Meng Huo</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: King of Southern Barbarians
	  
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Culprit:
You ignore the effects of BARBARIAN ASSAULT. You are considered as the source of damage from any BARBARIAN ASSAULT being played.

Resurgence:
During your draw phase, if you are damaged, you may skip your draw and reveal X cards from the top of the library. (X is your missing health.)
Discard each HEARTS card revealed and you gain 1 health; then take the remaining revealed cards into your hand.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Jiang Wei</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Dragon's Successor

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Provoke:
Once during your main phase, you may target a hero who has you within their attack range, that hero must play an ATTACK on you. If he does not, you choose and discard 1 card from that hero's hand, equipment zone, or judgment zone.

Recommence the Legacy: (Awakening Ability)
At the beginning of your turn, if you have no cards in your hand, gain 1 health or draw 2 cards, then reduce your max health by 1 and gain the [STARGAZING] ability.

[Stargazing]:
At the beginning of your turn, you may look at the top X cards of the library, where X is equal to the number of surviving heroes (Max 5); you may choose to put any number of these cards on top and bottom of the library in any order.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
	<Card>
      <cardName>Pang Tong</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Young Phoenix
      
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Shackles:
During you main phase, you may use a CLUBS suited card from your hand as IRON CHAINS; or recast that card.

Nirvana: (Limited Ability)
Whenever you are on the brink of death, you may discard all cards from your hand, equipment zone and judgement zone; if you do, flip your hero card face up, draw 3 cards and return to 3 health.
(You must choose to activate this ability before proceeding to resolve the Brink of Death state.)
      </cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Ma Su</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Arrogant Talent

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Talebearer:
Once during your main phase, you may discard a card and choose a target hero with the highest health, then you deal 1 damage to them.
(If there are several heroes with the highest health, you may choose one of them.)

Subdue the Barbarians:
Whenever you deal damage to another hero, you may prevent that damage. If you do, take 1 card from that hero's equipment or judgment zone into your hand.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Fa Zheng</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Supporter of Shu

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Reciprocation:
Whenever you gain 2 cards from another hero, you may have that hero draw a card.
Whenever you are dealt damage, for each damage, the source of damage chooses one of the following:
1. Source of damage gives you a card from their hand.
2. Source of damage loses 1 health.

Dazzle:
During your drawing phase, you may skip your draw and target another hero to draw 2 cards; then that hero must play an ATTACK on another hero of your choice within their attack range. If that hero does not, you take 2 cards from their hand inot your hand.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Xu Shu</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Loyal Gallant

Health/Gender:3M

Ability:

Silence:
All damage you deal or is dealt to you from tactics cards are prevented.

Recommendation:
At the end of your turn, you may discard a non-basic card from your hand or equipment zone to target another hero, that hero chooses one of the following:
1. Target hero draws 2 cards.
2. Target hero gain 1 health.
3. Target hero flips their hero face up and becomes unchained.

Note: Xu Shu is a Shu faction hero, his card shares the Wei color because in history he was forced to join Cao Cao due to having his mother held hostage, but he did not give any advice to Cao Cao after he joined him as he was still loyal to Liu Bei.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Liao Hua</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Veteran Who Has Gone Through the Vicissitudes of Life

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Vanguard:
At the beginning of your turn, you gain an extra main phase.

Aspirations: (Limited Ability)
Whenever you are on the brink of death, you may gain X health. (X is the number of factions in play). If you do, flip your hero card.
(You must choose to activate this ability before proceeding to resolve the Brink of Death state.)</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Guan Xing &amp; Zhang Bao</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Cubs of the Generals

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Paternal Souls:
During your main phase, you may discard 2 cards from your hand and have this be treated as playing an ATTACK.
(The color of the ATTACK has the same ruling as SERPENT HALBERD)
If this ATTACK deals damage, you gain the [SAINT WARRIOR] and [ROAR] abilities until the end of turn.

[Saint Warrior]:
You may play or discard any RED cards from your hand or equipment zone as an ATTACK.

[Roar]:
You may play any number of ATTACKs during your turn.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Ma Dai</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Entrusted During Crisis
	  
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Horsemanship:
The physical range you see other heroes is reduced by 1.

Sneak Attack:
At the beginning of your turn, you may draw a card, then discard a card. If you do, you may target a hero within your physical range, the target hero cannot play or discard cards with the same color as your discarded card until the end of your turn.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Guan Ping</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Son of the Saint Warrior
	  
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Dragon Roar:
Whenever a hero plays an ATTACK during their main phase, you may discard a card from your hand or equipment zone. If you do, that ATTACK does not count towards the ATTACK resctriction limit. If that ATTACK is red, you draw a card.
(ATTACK restriction limit: A hero is limted to playing one ATTACK per main phase unless another effect says otherwise.)</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Jian Yong</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Uninhibited Advisor
	  
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Fine Words:
At the beginning of your main phase, you may clash with another hero. If you win, the next basic or non-delay tactics card you use may target 1 additional or 1 less target. If you did not win, you cannot use tactics cards until the end of the turn.

Indulgence:
Whenever you win a clash, you may take the revealed card of the loser into your hand. Whenever you do not win a clash, you may take your revealed card back to your hand.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Liu Feng</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Tragic Foster Son
	  
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Framed:
At the beginning of your turn, you may choose up to 2 target heroes. Take one card from each hero's hand or equipment zone and attach them onto your hero card as [BETRAYAL] cards. Whenever a player wants to play an ATTACK on you, they may instead discard 2 [BETRAYAL] cards attached to your hero and treat it as playing an ATTACK on you.
(This ATTACK counts towards the ATTACK restriction limited. ATTACK restriction limit: A hero is limted to playing one ATTACK per main phase unless another effect says otherwise.)</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Wu Yi</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Cavalry of Shu
	  
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Rapid Assault:
Whenever you play a card during your turn, decrease your physical range with all other heroes by 1 until the end of turn. If your physical range with all other heroes is 1, cards you play ignore the effects of armor cards other heroes have equipped and your ATTACKs can target an additional hero.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhou Cang</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Shu Loyalist
	  
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Loyalty and Bravery:
After your ATTACK is resolved, you may give the ATTACK you played or the DODGE played by the defender to another target hero. (Other than yourself and the defender.)
If the card you give to the targeted hero is RED, the targeted hero who received the RED card may play an ATTACK targeting a hero within your attack range.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhang Song</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Waiting for a Worthy Emperor
	  
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Good memory:
At the start of your main phase, you may reveal a card from another hero's hand. Until the end of your turn, whenever you play a card with the same type as the revealed card, you draw a card.

Map offering:
At the start of each other hero's main phases, you may draw 2 cards then give that hero 2 cards from your hand. At the end of the turn, if he did not kill any hero, you lose 1 health.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Xia Hou Shi</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Whispering Beauty
	  
Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Gather Firewood:
At the end of each other hero's turn, if you and that hero have the same number of cards in hand, you may choose to let both of you draw a card.

Words of Swallow:
During your main phase, you may recast ATTACK cards. At the end of your main phase, if you have recasted 2 or more ATTACK cards, you may have target male hero draw 2 cards.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhang Ni</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Minority Soldier of Shu
	  
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Pacifying Barbarians:
Once during your main phase, you may choose a target hero. You and the target hero reveals a card from the hand at the same time. If you reveal an ATTACK and the target hero did not reveal a DODGE, you discard your ATTACK and deal 1 damage to the target hero. If you did not reveal an ATTACK and the target hero reveals a DODGE, you discard your revealed card and take a card from his hand or equipment zone into your hand.

Resolution:
If your current health is 1, your DODGE are treated as ATTACK.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Li Yan</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Shu Rations Officer
	  
Health/Gender:3M

Ability:

Rations Management:
Once during your main phase, you may take a card from another target hero's hand into your hand, then you choose one of the following:
1. That hero reveals the top 2 cards on top of the library, then takes all basic cards into their hand.
2. During that hero's next draw phase, that hero draws an additional card.

Insidious:
During your discard phase, cards that were put into your hand this turn do not count towards your max hand size limit.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Huang Hao</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Trickery Eunuch
	  
Health/Gender:3M

Ability:

Emperor's Crony:
At the end of your turn, you may target a hero who has the EMPEROR within their attack range; you discard a card from that hero's hand or equipment zone and then that hero draws a card. If he has more cards in their hand than the EMPEROR, you draw a card.

Bribery:
Once during each hero's turn, whenever you are dealt damage by another hero, you may reveal X cards in your hand and have that hero chooses one of the following:
1. Target hero takes a revealed card and prevent the damage.
2. Target hero discards X cards from their hand or equipment zone.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
	<Card>
      <cardName>Xia Hou Ba</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Backbone of Aspiration
	  
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Metamorphosing Panther:
If your current health is below 4, you gain the [PROVOKE] skill.
If your current health is below 4, you gain the [ROAR] skill.
If your current health is below 4, you gain the [GODLY SPEED] skill.

[Provoke]:
Once during your main phase, you may target a hero who has you within their attack range, that hero must play an ATTACK on you. If he does not, you choose and discard 1 card from that hero's hand, equipment zone, or judgment zone.

[Roar]:
You may play any number of ATTACK during your turn.

[Godly Speed]:
You may choose up to 3 of the following options:
1. Skip your judgment and draw phase.
2. Skip your main phase and discard an equipment card from your hand or equipment zone.
3. Skip your discard phase and flip your hero card.

For each option you have chosen, treat that as playing an ATTACK on any target hero, ignore any requirements for these ATTACK.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
	<Card>
      <cardName>Gan Fu Ren</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Empress of Shining Accomplishment
	  
Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Prudence:
Whenever you gain 1 health, you man target another hero to gain 1 health or draw a card.

Theosophy:
At the beginning of your turn, you may discard all cards in your hand. If the number of discarded cards was greater than your current health, you gain 1 health.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
	<Card>
      <cardName>Ma Liang</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Clever White Eyebrow Scholar
	  
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Autobiography:
During other hero's turns, if you gain any cards this turn, you must discard those cards at the end of the turn.
During your turn, whevener you gain cards, draw an additional card.
(Gaining cards from this skill does not trigger it.)

Promised Aid:
During your turn, if a card you play is resovled and is put into the discard pile, you may give that card to another hero. 
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
	<Card>
      <cardName>Zhang Xin Cai</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Respectful and Lamentable Empress
	  
Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Virtuos and Able:
Once during each hero's turn. whenever another hero discards a basic card, you may draw a card.

Dance with the Spear:
Once per main phase, you may perform a judgement, then until the end of the turn:
1. Your ATTACK cards with ranks lower than the rank of the judgement card have unlimited range.
2. Your ATTACK cards with ranks higher than the rank of the judgement card do not count towards the ATTACK restriction limit.
(ATTACK restriction limit: A hero is limted to playing one ATTACK per main phase unless another effect says otherwise.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
	<Card>
      <cardName>Ma Lun Yu</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Courageous and Mischievous
	  
Health/Gender: 4F

Ability:

Horsemanship:
The physical range you see other heroes is reduced by 1.

Phoenix Soul:
During your main phase, after targeting a single hero with your first ATTACK or DUEL this turn, you man choose to:
1. Draw X cards.
2. Increase tje damage being dealt by X.
(X is number of DIAMOND suited cards in the targeted hero's hand.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
	<Card>
      <cardName>Mi Zhu</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Trading Gold for Allies
	  
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Funding Assistance:
Once during your main phase, you may give any number of cards with rank total 13 to another target hero; then that hero gains 1 health.

Businessmen:
Your hand size limit is increased by +X.
At the beginning of the game, you draw X cards.
(X is your max health.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
	<Card>
      <cardName>Guan Suo</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Blissful Exalted Hero
	  
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Journey to Nanman:
When another hero dies, you may draw 3 cards; then choose to gain one ability:
1. [WARRIOR SAINT]
2. [VANGUARD]
3. [SUBDUE THE BARBARIANS]

Gathering Reputation:
The physical range you see other heroes is reduced by X.
(X is the number of surviving FEMALE heroes.)

[Saint Warrior]:
You may play or discard any RED cards from your hand or equipment zone as an ATTACK.

[Vanguard]:
At the beginning of your turn, you gain an extra main phase.

[Subdue the Barbarians]:
Whenever you deal damage to another hero, you may prevent that damage. If you do, take 1 card from that hero's equipment or judgment zone into your hand.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
	<Card>
      <cardName>Guan Yin Ping</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Battle Maiden
	  
Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Blood Sacrifice:
Once during your main phase, you may discard a RED card and target up to X heroes. The targeted heroes becomes chained and then you deal 1 FIRE damage to one of the targeted heroes.
(X is your missing health. If you are at full health, you may discard 1 card instead of X. You are not able to unchain heroes with this ability.)

Tiger Roar:
Whenever you deal FIRE damage, each hero who was dealt FIRE damage draws a card. You have no limit on the number of cards that can be used on these heroes until the end of turn.

Follow Heritage: (Awakening Ability)
At the end of your turn, if you have caused 3 or more damage this turn, you gain 1 max health and then gain 1 health. You lose the [TIGER ROAR] ability and take the "Azure Dragon Crescent Blade" equipment card from any surviving hero, the deck, or the discard pile into your hand.
(Unless the "Azure Dragon Crescent Blade" was removed by an ability or card effect, you should always be able to obtain it.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Qin Zai</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Words that Pierces the Heavens
	  
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Admonish Attack:
Whenever another hero uses an ATTACK on a target hero other than you, if you are within the attacker's attack range, you may place 1 card from your hand on top of the library and cancel all  targets from that ATTACK. If the ATTACK is not BLACK, you become the target of the ATTACK instead.

Expert Opponent:
Whenever you play an ATTACK on a target hero, you may clash with the that hero. If you win, your ATTACK cannot be cancelled by a DODGE.
Whenever you are the target of an ATTACK you can clash with the attacker. If you win, the effects of the ATTACK is cancelled.

Heavenly Defense:
Whenever you clash, you may use the top card of the library instead.
HEARTS suited cards you reveal during a clash are treated as a K rank.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
	<Card>
      <cardName>Wu Xian</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Empress of Mu Han
	  
Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Endless Blessing:
At the beginning of your turn, you may choose one:
1. You draw 1 additional card during your draw phase.
2. Once during this turn, your RED basic and non-delay tactics cards can target 1 additional player. (No range restrictions for the additional target)

If you have chosen a different option than your previous turn, add +1 to your chosen option's value for this turn, and then reset the values on this skill at the end of turn.

Abandon the Banquet:
At the end of your turn you may have another target hero takes 1 random HEARTS suited basic card from the deck. Then if that hero was the target of this skill in the previous turn, that hero loses 1 health.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
	<Card>
      <cardName>Sun Gan</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Defeating Enemies Through Diplomacy
	  
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Elegant Modesty:
Whenever you become the target of a non-delay tactics card, you may give any number of cards from your hand to another target hero.

Persuade for Alliance:
At the end of your main phase, you may clash with another target hero.
If you win, you are considered to have played SLEIGHT OF HAND.
If you lose, the targeted hero is considered to have played BURN BRIDGE targeting you.
(These actions may be cancelled by IMPECCABLE PLAN.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
	<Card>
      <cardName>Dong Yun</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Candid Speaking Minister
	  
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Righteousness:
At the end of your main phase, you may target a hero with cards in their hand not equal to their current health to draw a card or discard a card from their hand. If the number of cards in that hero's hand is now equal to their current health, you draw a card, and then give that hero a card.
(The targeted hero cbooses which card to discard.)

Feast:
Whenever you become the target of a non-delay tactics card, you may choose one:
1. Add an additional target. (Cannot target the hero who played it.) 
2. Remove a target. (The end result must still have at least 1 target.)
(This ability takes priority over multiple targeting tactics cards such as OATH OF PEACH GARDEN, BARBARIAN ASSAULT, HAIL OF ARROWS, and HARVEST. When resolving HARVEST, the cards are revealed before you may choose to remove a target.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
	<Card>
      <cardName>Zhuge Guo</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Basking in the Pagoda
	  
Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Avert Prayers:
Whenever you play an equipment card, you may take a random tool card from the deck.

Feathering:
Equipment and tactics cards do not count towards your max hand size limit.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
	<Card>
      <cardName>Ma Si</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Rejoining the South with Laughs
	  
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Frigid:
During your main phase, you may give an ATTACK card to a player that you haven't given one to yet. Before the end of their next turn, whenever they use the ATTACK card you have given them, you draw a card.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
	<Card>
      <cardName>Zhao Xiang</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Following the Dragon's Shadow
	  
Health/Gender: 4F

Ability:

Fragrant Spirit:
Whenever you deal damage with an ATTACK, you gain a [REFELCTION].
You may remove a [REFLECTION] to activate [DRAGON COURAGE] and draw a card.

Support the Han Dynasty: (Limited Ability)
At the beginning of your turn, you may remove all [REFLECTIONS] and draw 5 random SHU hero cards. Choose one of the 5 random SHU hero cards to replace your current hero, your max health is now equal to the number of [REFLECTIONS] you have removed during the game. If you are the hero with the lowest amount of current health, you gain 1 health.

[Dragon Courage]:
You may play or discard ATTACK cards as DODGE or vice versa.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
  </CardData>
</CardDataCollection>