<?xml version="1.0" encoding="Windows-1252"?>
<CardDataCollection xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <CardData>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Cao Cao</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Martial Emperor of Wei

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Villainous Hero:
Whenever you are dealt damage by a card effect, you may take that card into your hand.

Escort: (Emperor Ability)
Whenever you need to play or discard a DODGE, you may ask each other WEI faction hero to play or discard a DODGE for you, then it is treated as you playing the DODGE.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Cao Pi</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Great Empire Successor

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Unnatural Death:
When a hero dies, you may take all cards owned by that hero into your hand. (This happens before revealing the role)

Exile:
Whenever you are dealt damage, you may have target hero flip their hero card. If you do, that hero draw X cards. (X is your missing health)

Exaltation: (Emperor Ability)
Whenever another WEI faction hero's judgement is resolved, if that judgement card is BLACK, that hero may let you draw a card.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Cao Rui</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Talented Emperor

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Restoration:
Whenever you are dealt damage, you may have target hero perform a judgement, if the result is  that hero gains 1 health; if the result is BLACK, that hero draws X cards. (X is the amount of damage that was dealt to you).

Eagle Eye:
Once per hero's main phase, you may give all cards in your hand to another hero. If you do, that hero's hand size is increased by 1 and can use an additional ATTACK until the end of his next turn.

Boom and Bust: (Emperor Ability, Limited Ability)
When you are on brink of death, you may ask every other WEI faction hero in sequence to allow you to gain 1 health until every hero has respond. If they chose to have you gain health, they receive 1 damage after resolving this effect.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Si Ma Yi</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Ever Watchful Wolf

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Retaliation:
Whenever you are dealt damage by a hero, you may take 1 card from that hero's hand or equipment zone.

Demonic Talent:
Whenever a hero performs a judgement, you may replace the judgement card with a card from your hand. The judgement is resolved with the new card.
(You do not take the initial judgement card into you hand)</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Xiahou Dun</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: One-Eyed Warrior

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Staunch:
Whenever you are dealt damage, you may perform a judgement. If the result is not a Heart suit, the source of damage chooses one:
1. Source of damage discards 2 cards from their hand
2. Source of damage takes 1 damage</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhang Liao</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: General of the Vanguard

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Ambush:
At the beginning of your draw phase, you may skip your draw. If you do, you may take 1 card from the hand of up to 2 target heroes.
(You may target the same hero twice.)</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Xu Zhu</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Crazy Tiger

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Bare-chested: 
You can choose to draw 1 card less during your draw phase. If you do, during your next main phase your ATTACK and DUEL cards deal 1 additional damage.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Guo Jia</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Prophet with An Early End

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Heaven's Envy:
Whenever your judgment is resolved, put that judgment card into your hand

Bestowed Rouse:
Whenever you are dealt damage, for each damage you receive, look at 2 cards on top of the library and then give each card to any number of target heroes. (Can be the same target hero)</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhen Ji</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Unfortunate Beauty

Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Gorgeous Beauty:
You may play or use any BLACK cards in your hand as a DODGE.

Goddess of Luo:
At the beginning of your turn, you may perform a judgement; if the result is BLACK, take that card into your hand and repeat this process again.
(If the result is RED, the revealed card is discarded and the process ends.)</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Xia Hou Yuan</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Lightning Panther

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Extreme Speed:
You may choose up to 3 of the following options:
1. Skip your judgment and draw phase.
2. Skip your main phase and discard an equipment card from your hand or equipment zone.
3. Skip your discard phase and flip your hero card.

For each option you have chosen, treat that as playing an ATTACK on any target hero, ignore any  requirements for these ATTACK.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Cao Ren</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Great General

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Entrench:
At the end of your turn, you may flip your hero card. If you do, draw 4 cards then discard a card. If the discarded card is an equipment, you play that card instead.

Rescue from Siege:
You may play cards in your equipment zone as IMPECCABLE PLAN.
When your hero card is flipped to the face up position, you may discard a card. If you do, you may move a card from a target hero's equipment or judgment zone to another target hero's equipment or judgment zone</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Dian Wei</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Ancient Berserker

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Assault:
Once during your main phase, you may lose 1 health or discard an equipment card; If you do, you deal 1 damage to a target hero.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Xun Yu</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Genius Advisor

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Rouse the Tiger:
Once during your main phase, you may clash with a hero with more health than you. If you did not win, that hero deals 1 damage to you.
If you win, choose another target hero within the attack range of the loser. The loser deals 1 damage to that hero.

Eternal Loyalty:
Whenever you are dealt damage, for each damage you receive, choose a target hero to draw X cards (X is the difference between the number of cards from that hero's hand and maximum health, max 5)</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Xu Huang</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Reminiscence of Zhou Ya Fu

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Blockade:
During your main phase, you may play a BLACK card from your hand or BLACK equipment cards as RATIONS DEPLETED.
You may play RATIONS DEPLETED on heroes within a physical  of 2.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhang He</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Military Clairvoyant

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Flexibility: 
During you turn, you may discard a card from your hand to skip one of your turn phases. (Except the start of turn and end of turn)

If you skip:
1. Draw Phase: Choose 2 target heroes and take 1 card from each of their hands into your hand.
2. Main Phase: You may move an equipment card to another empty equipment zone, or move an judgment card to another empty judgment zone.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Deng Ai</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Staunch Warrior

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Strategic Farming:
Whenever you play a card from your hand, or discard a card from your hand or equipment zone outside your turn, you perform a judgement.
If the result is not a HEART suit, you attach the judgement card on your hero card. That card is now considered as a [FIELD].

The physical range you see other heroes is reduced by X, where X is number of [FIELD] cards attached to you.

Dangerous Exploration: (Awakening Ability)
At the beginning of your turn, if you have 3 or more [FIELD] cards, reduce your maximum health by 1 and gain the [BLITZ] ability.

[Blitz]:
You may play a [FIELD] as a PILFER.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Cao Zhi</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Virtuoso Poet

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Falling Bloom:
Whenever another hero discards a CLUB suited card or their CLUB suited judgement card is put into the graveyard, you may place any number of them into your hand.

Drunken Quatrain:
Whenever you want to play a WINE, if your hero card is facing up, you may flip it face down. If you do, it is considered that you have played a WINE.

Whenever you are dealt damage, if you hero card is facing down, you may flip it face up.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Yu Jin</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Mainstay of Wei Military

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Commander:
At the beginning of your turn, you may target a hero with a number of cards in their hand greater than their current health and discard X cards from their hand or equipment zone (X is the difference between the cards in their hand and their current health), then you choose one of the following:
1. For each non-equipment card discarded card, you must discard a card from your hand or equipment zone.
2. The target hero draws X cards.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhang Chun Hua</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Cold-blooded Empress

Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Heartless:
All damage dealt by you is considered as loss of health. 

Bereavement:
Whenever you have less than X cards in your hand, draw until you have X cards. (X is your missing health)</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Cao Zhang</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Yellow Bearded General

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Versatile Fighter:
During your draw phase, you may skip your draw and choose 1 of the following:
1. Draw 3 cards, until the end of your turn you cannot play or discard an ATTACK in response to card effects.
2. Draw 1 card, until end of your turn, you may use an additional ATTACK and ignore the attack range requirements for your ATTACK cards.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Xun You</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Advisor of Wei

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Contrivance:
Once during your main phase, you may use any card from your hand as any non-delay tactics card.

Playing Dumb:
Whenever you are dealt damage, you may draw a card and reveal your hand; if all cards in your hand are of the same color, the source of damage discards a card from their hand.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhong Hui</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Audacious Schemer

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Ambition:
Whenever you are dealt damage, for each damage you receive, you draw a card, then select a card from you hand and attach it face up to your hero as a [POWER].
You hand size is increased by X. (X is the number of [POWER] attached to you)

Insurrection: (Awakening Ability)
At the beginning of your turn, if you have 3 or more [POWER], you gain 1 health or draw 2 cards, then reduce your max health by 1 and gain [ERADICATE].

[Eradicate]:
Once during your main phase, you may discard a [POWER] and target a hero, that hero draws 2 cards. If the number of cards in the hero's hand is greater than yours, you deal 1 damage to him.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Wang Yi</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Elated Heroine

Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Chastity:
Whenever you become the target of an ATTACK or a non-delay tactics card played by a hero, you may lose 1 health. If you do, ignore the effects of that card targeting you and then discard a card from that hero's hand or equipment zone.

Secret Plan:
At the end of your turn, you may draw X cards, then may give X cards in your hand to another hero. (X is the amount of life you have lost)</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Cao Chong</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Benevolent Child Prodigy

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Weight the Elephant:
Whenever you are dealt damage, for each damage taken, reveal the top 4 cards of the deck. You place any number of revealed cards with rank total less than or equal to 13 into your hand.

Benevolence:
Whenever another hero wtih 1 health is dealt damage, you can flip your hero card and discard an equipment card to prevent all damage from the source.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Guo Huai</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Governor of West

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Refined Strategy:
At the end of your main phase, if the number of cards you have used is greater than your health, you may draw 2 cards.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Man Chong</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Political and Military Strategist

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Torture:
Once during your main phase, you may discard any number of cards from your hand and target another hero, that hero must choose one:
1. Discard a card from their hand or equipment zone that has a different type than the cards you've discard.
2. Flip his hero card and draw that many cards that you have discarded.

Defensive Strategy:
Whenever you are dealt damage, you may reveal a card from you hand. The source of damage must discard a card from their hand or equipment zone with a different type than your revealed card. If he does not, you gain 1 health.

(The card types are: basic, equipment, tactics)</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Cao Zhen</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Pillar of Wei

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Defense Minister:
At the beginning of each other hero's main phase, you may discard a card from your hand with same color as one of your equipments. If you do, that hero cannot play or use any cards with the same color. At the end of the main phase, if he has not played an ATTACK, this is treated as you playing an ATTACK on him.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Han Hao &amp; Shi Huan</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Commander of Central Army

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Careful Decision:
Whenever you discard a BLACK basic card into the graveyard, you may play it as RATIONS DEPLETED on any hero.

Courageous Plan:
At the beginning of each other hero's judgement phase, you may discard a card from his judgement zone. If you do, treat this as you playing an ATTACK towards that hero. If the ATTACK does not deal damage, you draw a card.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Chen Qun</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Role Model of All Courtiers

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Rank Determination:
During your main phase, you may discard a card from your hand and target a damaged hero; that hero performs a judgement. (You cannot discard cards which have the same type to other cards you have played or discarded this turn)
If the result is BLACK, that hero draws X cards and you cannot use [RANK DETERMNINATION] on that hero again. (X is that hero's missing heath)
If the result is RED, you filp your hero card.

Justice and Mercy:
Whenever a hero is flipped or chained, you may let that hero draw a card.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Cao Xiu</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Talented Cavalry

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Swift Horse:
The physical range you see other heroes is reduced by X. (X is your missing health)

Flanking:
Whenever your ATTACK deals damage to a target hero, if you have a weapon equipped, you may ask that hero to choose one:
1. Discard X cards from their hand (X is the attack range of the weapon), then you discard the weapon card.
2. Increase the damage of this ATTACK by +1.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhong Yao</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Creator of Block Calligraphy

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Calligraphy Master:
Whenever you want to play a basic card, you may put a BLACK non-basic card on top of the library; you may name a basic card and this is treated as you playing the named card. (You cannot use this ability to play a card you've already played previously this turn)

Formulate:
Whenever a hero plays a BLACK card targeting at least one hero during their main phase, you may let one of the targets draw a card.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Empress Guo</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Undefiled Queen 

Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Forging Edict:
Once per main phase, you may reveal a card from your hand, and then target a hero with the closest physical range to you. That hero announces a basic card name. Until the end of your turn you may treat your revealed card as the announced card. (You cannot be the target of the announced card.)
Upgrade 1: Once per main phase, you may reveal a card from your hand, and then target a hero with the closest physical range to you. That hero announces a basic or non-delay tactics card name. Until the end of your turn you may treat your revealed card as the announced card. (You cannot be the target of the announced card.)
Upgrade 2: Once per main phase, you may treat a card in your hand as any basic or non-delay tactics card. (You cannot be the target of the announced card)

Brain racking:
Whenever you are dealt damage, you may draw a card or upgrade [FORGING EDICT]. (Max 2 times)</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Sun Zi &amp; Liu Fang</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Dual Who Speaks with Forked Tongue

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Bluffing:
During your discard phase, if you have discarded at least 2 cards with different suits, you may gain 1 health or draw a card.

Flattery:
Once during each hero's main phase, if you have a card that you can play in your hand, you may target a hero and that hero discards a card from their hand, then you cannot play a card with the same suit as the discarded card for the rest of this turn. If the discarded card is a SPADE suit, you flip your hero card and lose 1 health.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Xin Xian Ying</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Prestigiously Wise Noblewoman

Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Loyalty:
Once during your main phase, you may reveal 1 card from your hand, then choose a target hero with a hand size that is greater than their current health to reveal X cards from their hand. (X is the difference between hand cards and current HP) Compare the revealed cards and apply the following:
1. If at least 1 of that hero's revealed cards has the same color as your card, you draw 1 card from the deck or discard 1 card from that hero.
2. If at least 1 of that hero's revealed cards has the same rank as your card, change this ability to TWICE DURING YOUR TURN.
3. If there are no color or ranks matching, your hand size limit is reduced by 1 for the rest of the game.

Ability and Insight:
At the beginning of your draw phase, you may choose one:
1. Your hand size limit is increased by +1 for the rest of the game; and you cannot play cards targeting other heroes until the end of turn.
2. Gain 1 health and you cannot play cards on yourself until the end of turn.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Ji Kang</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Lonely and Peaceful in the High Peaks

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Gentle Chords:
Whenever you are dealt damage, you may choose to have the source of damage:
1. Lose 1 health and equip a random equipment from the deck. (Draw until an equipment is reveal, then return the rest of the cards back and shuffle the deck)
2. Gain 1 health and discard 1 equipment.

Whenever you gain health, you may choose another target hero to:
1. Lose 1 health and equip a random equipment from the deck. (Draw until an equipment is reveal, then return the rest of the cards back and shuffle the deck) 
2. Gain 1 health and discard 1 equipment.

If the equipment card played or discarded was CLUBS suited, you draw a card.

Soundless:
When you are dead, you may choose a target hero to randomly gain a ability from [GENTLE CHORD MANUSCRIPT]. Until the beginning of his next turn, that hero cannot be the target of CLUBS suited cards.
(Assign a suit to each ability on [GENTLE CHORD MANUSCRIPT], then reveal a card from the deck to determine the ability being gained.) </cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Gentle Chords Manuscript</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Ability:
	  
Harmonious Chord:
Whenever you gain health, you may choose another target hero to gain 1 health and discard an equipment.

Gentle Chord:
Whenever you are dealt damage, you may have the source of damage gain 1 health and discard an equipment.

Intense Chord:
Whenever you gain health, you may choose another target hero to lose 1 health and equip a random equipment from the deck.

Violent Chord:
Whenever you are dealt damage, you may have the source of damage lose 1 health and equip a random equipment from the deck. (Draw until an equipment is reveal, then return the rest of the cards back and shuffle the deck)</cardDescription>
    </Card>
  </CardData>
</CardDataCollection>