<?xml version="1.0" encoding="Windows-1252"?>
<CardDataCollection xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <CardData>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Cao Cao</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Martial Emperor of Wei

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Villainous Hero:
Whenever you are dealt damage by a card effect, you may draw a card from the library or take the card that damaged you into your hand.
(You may only activate this abilty per each instance of damage.)

Escort: (Emperor Ability)
Whenever you need to play or discard a DODGE, you may ask each other WEI faction hero to play or discard a DODGE for you, then it is treated as you playing the DODGE.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Cao Pi</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Great Empire Successor

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Unnatural Death:
When a hero dies, you may take all the cards owned by that hero into your hand.
(This happens before revealing their role card.)

Banish to Exile:
Whenever you are dealt damage, you may have a target hero flip their hero card. If you do, that hero draws X cards.
(X is your missing health.)

Exaltation: (Emperor Ability)
Whenever another WEI faction hero's judgement is resolved, if that judgement card is BLACK, that hero may let you draw a card.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Cao Rui</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Talented Emperor

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Restoration:
Whenever you are dealt damage, you may have a target hero perform a judgement, if the result is RED that hero gains 1 health; if the result is BLACK, that hero draws X cards.
(X is the amount of damage that was dealt to you).

Brilliant Idea:
Once per a hero's main phase, you may give all cards in your hand to another hero. If you do, that hero's hand size is increased by 1 and can use an additional ATTACK until the end of their next turn.

The Rise and Fall: (Emperor Ability, Limited Ability)
When you are on brink of death, you may ask each other target WEI faction hero in sequence to allow you to gain 1 health until every hero has respond. If a target hero chose to allow you gain health, they receive 1 damage after resolving this effect.
(You must choose to activate this ability before proceeding to resolve the Brink of Death state.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Si Ma Yi</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Ever Watchful Wolf

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Retaliation:
Whenever you are dealt damage, for each point of damage recieved, you may take 1 card from the hand or equipment zone of the source of damage.

Demonic Talent:
Whenever a hero performs a judgement, you may replace the judgement card with a card from your hand or equipment zone. The judgement is resolved with the new card.
(You do not take the initial judgement card into you hand.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Xiahou Dun</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The One-Eyed Demon

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Staunch:
Whenever you are dealt damage by a hero, for each dmage recieved, you may perform a judgement.
If the result is RED, the source of damage takes 1 damage.
If the result is BLACK, you discard a card from the source of damage.

Frugal:
Whenever you gain cards outside of your draw phase, you may attach any number of the cards you've gain face down onto your hero. At the end of this turn, you give all the attached cards to another target hero.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Xiahou Dun</cardName>
	  <portraitOverride>Xiahou Dun02</portraitOverride>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The One-Eyed Wolf

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Indignation
Whenever you are dealt damage, you may turn your health bar card upright.
Whenever your health bar card is upright, all damage you would recieve is prevent.
(This ability does not activate or prevent damage from loss of health.)

Avenge:
At the end of each hero's turn, if you health bar card is upright, return it back to normal and choose one:
1. Discard X cards from the active hero. (X is the difference between the number of cards in your hand and maximum health.)
2. Choose a target hero, this is treated as you playing an ATTACK to the targeted hero.
(The ATTACK has no color or element.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhang Liao</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: General of the Vanguard

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Ambush:
At the beginning of your draw phase, you may choose to draw X fewer cards. Then choose X target heros and take a card from each of their hands.
(X is the number of heroes with more cards in their hand than you. If the number of heroes with more cards in their hand than you is greater than what you are able to draw, you do not draw and continue resolving the rest of this ability. You cannot take more than 1 card from a hero.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Xu Zhu</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Crazy Tiger

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Bare-chested: 
During your draw phase, you may skip your draw and reveal 3 cards from the top of the deck; then take any basic, weapon, and DUEL cards into your hand and discard the rest.
Until the start of your next turn, ATTACK and DUEL cards you play deal +1 additional damage.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Guo Jia</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Prophet with An Early End

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Heaven's Envy:
Whenever your judgment is resolved, take the judgment card into your hand.

Bestowed Rouse:
Whenever you are dealt damage, for each point of damage you receive, draw 2 cards and then attach up to 2 cards from you hand on to any target heroes face down. The heroes with the attached cards take them into their hand at the beginning of their next draw phase.
(You may choose to not to attach cards onto other heroes. You may attach 2 cards to a hero instead of 1 card to 2 heroes. If you recieve more than 1 damage per instance, you can activate this ability as many times as the damage recieved, but you must resolve each instance completely before activating it again. You must be saved from the brink of death in order to activate this ability.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhen Ji</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Unfortunate Beauty

Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Gorgeous Beauty:
You may play or use any BLACK cards in your hand as a DODGE.

Goddess of Luo:
At the beginning of your turn, you may perform a judgement; if the result is BLACK, take that card into your hand and repeat this process again.
(If the result is RED, the revealed card is discarded and the process ends.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Xiahou Yuan</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Lightning Panther

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Godly Speed:
You may choose up to 3 of the following options:
1. Skip your judgment and draw phase.
2. Skip your main phase and discard an equipment card from your hand or equipment zone.
3. Skip your discard phase and flip your hero card.

For each option you have chosen, treat that as playing an ATTACK on any target hero, ignore any requirements for these ATTACK.
(These ATTACKs are colorless and do not have an element attached to them.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Cao Ren</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Great General

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Entrench:
At the end of your turn, you may flip your hero card. If you do, draw 4 cards and then discard a card. If the discarded card is an equipment, you play that card instead.

Rescue from Siege:
You may play cards in your equipment zone as IMPECCABLE PLAN.
When your hero card is flipped to the face up position, you may discard a card. If you do, you may move a card from a target hero's equipment or judgment zone to another target hero's equipment or judgment zone.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Cao Ren</cardName>
	  <portraitOverride>Cao Ren02</portraitOverride>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Never Running From Danger

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Discipline:
Once per your main phase, you may lose 1 health and choose to view the cards from a target hero's hand.
If there is a DODGE, reveal it and treat this as you playing an ATTACK on the targeted hero; the physical range between you and the targeted hero is 1 until the end of this turn.
If there is not a DODGE, you discard one card from the targeted hero. 

Break Through:
At the end of your turn, you may choose any number of heroes with missing health to draw a card.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Dian Wei</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Ancient Berserker

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Assault:
Once during your main phase, you may lose 1 health or discard an equipment card; If you do, you deal 1 damage to a target hero.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Xun Yu</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Genius Advisor

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Rouse the Tiger:
Once during your main phase, you may clash with a hero with more health than you. If you did not win, that hero deals 1 damage to you.
If you win, choose another target hero within the attack range of the loser. The loser deals 1 damage to that hero.

Eternal Loyalty:
Whenever you are dealt damage, for each point of damage you receive, choose a target hero to draw X cards.
(X is the difference between the number of cards from that hero's hand and maximum health, max 5.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Xu Huang</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Reminiscence of Zhou Ya Fu

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Blockade:
During your main phase, you may play BLACK basic or equipment cards as RATIONS DEPLETED.
You may play RATIONS DEPLETED on heroes within a physical range of 2 from you.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhang He</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Military Clairvoyant

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Flexibility: 
During you turn, you may discard a card from your hand to skip one of your turn phases.
(Except the start of turn and end of turn)

If you skip:
1. Draw Phase: Choose 2 target heroes and take 1 card from each of their hands.
2. Main Phase: You may move an equipment card to another empty equipment zone, or move an judgment card to another empty judgment zone.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Deng Ai</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Staunch Warrior

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Strategic Farming:
Whenever you play a card from your hand, or discard a card from your hand or equipment zone outside of your turn, you perform a judgement.
If the result is not a HEARTS suit, you attach the judgement card on your hero card. That card is now considered as a [FIELD].

The physical range you see other heroes is reduced by X, where X is number of [FIELD] cards attached to you.

Dangerous Exploration: (Awakening Ability)
At the beginning of your turn, if you have 3 or more [FIELD] cards, reduce your maximum health by 1 and gain the [BLITZ] ability.

[Blitz]:
You may play a [FIELD] as a PILFER.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Cao Zhi</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Virtuoso Poet

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Falling Bloom:
Whenever another hero discards a CLUBS suited card or their CLUBS suited judgement card is put into the graveyard, you may take any number of them into your hand.

Drunken Quatrain:
Whenever you want to play a WINE, if your hero card is facing up, you may flip it face down. If you do, it is treated as if you have played a WINE.

Whenever you are dealt damage, if you hero card is facing down, you may flip it face up.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Yu Jin</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Mainstay of Wei Military

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Commander:
At the beginning of your turn, you may target a hero with an amount of cards in their hand greater than their current health and discard X cards from their hand or equipment zone (X is the difference between the cards in their hand and their current health), then you choose one of the following:
1. For each non-equipment card discarded, you must discard a card from your hand or equipment zone.
2. The targeted hero draws X cards.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhang Chun Hua</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Cold-blooded Empress

Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Heartless:
All damage dealt by you is considered as loss of health.
(Loss of health is different than dealing damage, you are not considered to have dealt damage when a hero has loss health.)

Bereavement:
Whenever you have less than X cards in your hand, draw until you have X cards. (X is your missing health.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Cao Zhang</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Yellow Bearded General

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Versatile Fighter:
During your draw phase, you may skip your draw and choose 1 of the following:
1. Draw 3 cards, until the end of your turn you cannot play or discard an ATTACK in response to card effects.
2. Draw 1 card, until end of your turn, you may use an additional ATTACK and ignore the attack range requirements for your ATTACK cards.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Xun You</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Advisor of Wei

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Contrivance:
Once during your main phase, you may use any card from your hand as any non-delay tactics card.

Playing Dumb:
Whenever you are dealt damage, you may draw a card and reveal your hand; if all cards in your hand are of the same color, the source of damage discards a card from their hand.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhong Hui</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Audacious Schemer

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Ambition:
Whenever you are dealt damage, for each point of damage you receive, you draw a card, then choose a card from you hand and attach it face up to your hero as a [POWER].
You hand size is increased by X. (X is the number of [POWER] cards attached to you.)

Insurrection: (Awakening Ability)
At the beginning of your turn, if you have 3 or more [POWER] cards attached, you gain 1 health or draw 2 cards, then reduce your max health by 1 and gain [ERADICATE].

[Eradicate]:
Once during your main phase, you may discard a [POWER] card and target a hero, that hero draws 2 cards. If the number of cards in the hero's hand is greater than yours, you deal 1 damage to him.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Wang Yi</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Elated Heroine

Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Chastity:
Whenever you become the target of an ATTACK or a non-delay tactics card played by a hero, you may lose 1 health. If you do, ignore the effects of that card targeting you and then discard a card from that hero's hand or equipment zone.

Secret Plan:
At the end of your turn, you may draw X cards, then may give X cards in your hand to another hero. (X is the amount of life you have lost.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Cao Chong</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Benevolent Child Prodigy

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Weight the Elephant:
Whenever you are dealt damage, reveal the top 4 cards of the library. You place any number of revealed cards with rank totaling less than or equal to 13 into your hand.
(Ace is is the lowest with a value of 1, King is highest a value of 13.)

Benevolence:
Whenever another hero wtih 1 health is being dealt damage, you may flip your hero card and discard an equipment card to prevent all damage from the source.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Guo Huai</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Governor of West

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Refined Strategy:
At the end of your main phase, if the number of cards you have used is greater than your health, you may draw 2 cards.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Man Chong</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Political and Military Strategist

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Torture:
Once during your main phase, you may discard any number of cards from your hand and target another hero, that hero must choose one:
1. Discard a card from their hand or equipment zone that has a different type than the cards you've discard.
2. Flip his hero card and draw that many cards that you have discarded.

Defensive Strategy:
Whenever you are dealt damage, you may reveal a card from you hand. The source of damage must discard a card from their hand or equipment zone with a different type than your revealed card. If he does not, you gain 1 health.
(The card types are: basic, equipment, tactics.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Guan Yu</cardName>
	  <portraitOverride>Guan Yu02</portraitOverride>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Marquis of Han Shou

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Saint Warrior:
You may play or discard any RED cards from your hand or equipment zone as an ATTACK.

Lone Rider: (Awakening ability)
At the beginning of your turn, if you have more cards in your hand than your current health and the EMPEROR is Cao Cao, reduce your max health by 1 and gain the [HORSEMANSHIP] and [ROAR] abilities. 

[Horsemanship]:
The physical range you see other heroes is reduced by 1.

[Roar]:
You may play any number of ATTACKs during your turn.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Pang De</cardName>
	  <portraitOverride>Pang De02</portraitOverride>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Ascend with Enlightenment

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Horsemanship:
The physical range you see other heroes is reduced by 1.

Implacable:
During your main phase, you may discard an ATTACK and choose to target a hero within your attack range to discard a card. If the discarded card is not an ATTACK and your health is less than or equal to the targeted hero, treat this as you playing a DUEL targeting that hero.
(The DUEL can be cancelled with an IMPECCABLE PLAN.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Cai Wen Ji</cardName>
	  <portraitOverride>Cai Wen Ji02</portraitOverride>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Talented Woman Desiring to Return

Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Showing Affection:
Once per round, whenever a hero enters the brink of death, you may choose another target hero to draw 4 cards; then the targeted hero must discards 4 cards. If each discarded card has a different suit, this is treated as the targeted hero playing a PEACH for the hero on the brink of death.

Silent Knowledge:
At the end of your turn, you may play a card from your hand as the first basic or tactics card you have played this turn.
Then you may play another card from your hand as the second basic or tactics card you have played this turn.
(You must play the first card before being able to play the second card for their effects.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Jia Xu</cardName>
	  <portraitOverride>Jia Xu02</portraitOverride>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Godly Foresight

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Thorough Scheme:
Your non-delay tactics cards cannot be cancelled by IMPECCABLE PLAN.
You cannot be the target of delay tactics cards.
(If LIGHTNING BOLT is in play, it does not enter your judgement zone and skips you in turn priority.)

Between Books: (Limited Ability)
Once per game, during you main phase, you can give a BLACK card from your hand to a target hero; then choose another hero within the targeted hero's attack range, both targeted heroes perform a clash. The winner of the clash discards 2 cards and the loser loses 1 health.

Own Wife: (Limited Ability)
Once per game, whenever you are dealt damage, you may have another MALE hero increase their max health by +1; if that hero has a Emperor Ability and isn't the current Emperor, that hero gains his Emperor Ability.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Jiang Wei</cardName>
	  <portraitOverride>Jiang Wei02</portraitOverride>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Young Unicorn

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Stranded:
At the end of your turn, lose 1 health and draw 2 cards.

(Upgrade):
At the end of your turn, you may lose 1 health and draw 2 cards.

Meet the Light: (Awakening Ability)
Whenever you enter the brink of death, reduce your max health by -1, return to 2 health, gain the [PROVOKE] ability and upgrade [STRANDED}.

[Provoke]:
Once during your main phase, you may target a hero who has you within their attack range, that hero must play an ATTACK on you. If he does not, you choose and discard 1 card from that hero's hand, equipment zone, or judgment zone.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Cao Zhen</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Pillar of Wei

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Defense Minister:
At the beginning of each other hero's main phase, you may discard a card from your hand with same color as one of your equipments. If you do, that hero cannot play or use any cards with the same color. At the end of their main phase, if the targeted hero has not played an ATTACK, this is treated as you playing an ATTACK on him.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Han Hao &amp; Shi Huan</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Commander of Central Army

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Careful Decision:
Whenever you discard a BLACK basic card into the graveyard, you may play it as RATIONS DEPLETED on any hero.

Courageous Plan:
At the beginning of each other hero's judgement phase, you may discard a card from his judgement zone. If you do, treat this as you playing an ATTACK towards that hero. If the ATTACK does not deal damage, you draw a card.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Chen Qun</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Role Model of All Courtiers

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Rank Determination:
During your main phase, you may discard a card from your hand and target a damaged hero; that hero performs a judgement. (You cannot discard cards which have the same type to other cards you have played or discarded this turn)
If the result is BLACK, that hero draws X cards and you cannot use [RANK DETERMNINATION] on that hero again. (X is that hero's missing heath)
If the result is RED, you filp your hero card.

Justice and Mercy:
Whenever a hero is flipped or chained, you may let that hero draw a card.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Cao Xiu</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Talented Cavalry

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Swift Horse:
The physical range you see other heroes is reduced by X. (X is your missing health)

Flanking:
Whenever your ATTACK deals damage to a target hero, if you have a weapon equipped, you may ask that hero to choose one:
1. Discard X cards from their hand (X is the attack range of the weapon), then you discard the weapon card.
2. Increase the damage of this ATTACK by +1.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhong Yao</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Creator of Block Calligraphy

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Calligraphy Master:
Whenever you want to play a basic card, you may put a BLACK non-basic card on top of the library; you may name a basic card and this is treated as you playing the named card.
(You cannot use this ability to play a card you have already played this turn.)

Formulate:
Whenever another hero plays a BLACK card targeting at least one hero during their main phase, if no hero is dealt damage by that card, you may choose one of the targeted heroes to draw a card.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Empress Guo</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Undefiled Queen 

Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Forging Edict:
Once per main phase, you may reveal a card from your hand, and then target a hero with the closest physical range to you. That hero announces a basic card name. Until the end of your turn you may treat your revealed card as the announced card. (You cannot and will not be the target of the announced card.)

(Upgrade 1):
Once per main phase, you may reveal a card from your hand, and then target a hero with the closest physical range to you. That hero announces a basic or non-delay tactics card name. Until the end of your turn you may treat your revealed card as the announced card. (You cannot be the target of the announced card.)

(Upgrade 2):
Once per main phase, you may treat a card in your hand as any basic or non-delay tactics card. (You cannot be the target of the announced card)

Brain racking:
Whenever you are dealt damage, you may draw a card or upgrade [FORGING EDICT]. (Max 2 times)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Sun Zi &amp; Liu Fang</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Dual Who Speaks with Forked Tongue

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Bluffing:
During your discard phase, if you have discarded at least 2 cards with different suits, you may gain 1 health or draw a card.

Flattery:
Once during each hero's main phase, if you have a card that you can play in your hand, you may target a hero and that hero discards a card from their hand, then you cannot play a card with the same suit as the discarded card for the rest of this turn. If the discarded card is a SPADES suit, you flip your hero card and lose 1 health.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Li Dian</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Understanding and Righteous

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Sincerity:
At the beginning of your turn, you may look at the top 4 cards of the library; then choose 2 to be placed back on top of the library and 2 to be placed on the bottom of the library.

Flattery:
Whenever you deal damage to a hero or is dealt damage by a hero, you may both draw a card.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Si Ma Zhao</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: A Man of Sinister Ambition

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Transparent:
At the beginning of your main phase, you may reveal all the cards in your hand; then choose a target hero within your attack range, this is treated as you playing an ATTACK on the targeted hero.
(The ATTACK you produce with this ability has no color or element. You may use weapon effects for the ATTACK you produce with this ability.)

Careful Wolf:
Whenever you are dealt damage, for each point of damage you receive, you may perform a judgement; you may discard a card from your hand to replace the judgement result with the discard card.
Then veiw the cards from the hand of the source of damage, you may discard any number of cards that share the same suit as the judgment result.
(You may choose just view the cards in their hand and not to discard any cards at all.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Wang Yuan Ji</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Civilized Queen

Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Snuff Rebellion:
Once during your main phase, you may discard 3 cards of the same suit and choose a target hero in your attack range to flip their hero card. You cannot play ATTACKs until the end of your turn.

Virtue:
At the end of your turn, you may draw cards until the number of cards in your hand is equal to your max health.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Yang Xiu</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Genius Unrestrained

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Have Your Cake:
Whenever you become the target of a tactics card and you are not the only target, you may immediately draw a card; then ignore the effects of the tactics card.

The Wishing Bone:
Whenever you are dealt damage, you may announce a card type. The source of damage cannot play or discard cards that share the same typing as the announced card for the rest of the turn.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Chen Lin</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: His Pen Can Cleave Bamboo

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Cutting Pen:
At the end of your turn you may attach a card from your hand face down on another hero without a [PEN]. At the beginning of a hero's turn, if they have a [PEN] attached, they must look at the [PEN] card and choose one:
1. Give you one card from their hand with the same type as the [PEN] card and then take the [PEN] card into their hand.
2. Removed the [PEN] card attached to their hero, then lose 1 health.

Eulogize:
During your main phase, you may target a hero. If the amount of cards in the targeted hero's hand is greater than their current health, they discard 2 cards. If their current health is greather than the amount of cards in their hand, they draw 2 cards. You may only target each hero once per game.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Cao Ang</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Pay the Price for Justice

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Generous Anger:
Whenever a hero becomes the target of an ATTACK, if the physical distance between you and the targeted hero is 1, you may draw a card, then reveal a card from your hand and give it to that hero. If the revealed card is an equipement, the targeted hero may equip it immediately.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Yue Jin</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Determined to Overcome

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Brave and Resolute:
Once during the end of each other hero's turn, you may discard a basic card and have that hero choose one:
1. The targeted hero discards a card and have you draw a card.
2. You deal 1 damage to the targeted hero.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Cheng Yu</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Generation's Eccentric

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Amush:
At the end of your turn, you may attach a card from your hand face down onto your hero as an [AMBUSH], and assign a basic or tactics name to it.
During another hero's turn, when a hero plays a card, you may remove an [AMBUSH] sharing the same name as the card being played to cancel the effects of the card.
(You may only have one card of that named attached at a time. Card effects that target multiple heros are immdiately cancel and resolved, you must choose to use this ability before allowing the effects of any card to continue being resolved.)

Fertility:
Whenever you are dealt damage, you may choose one:
1. Draw cards until you have X cards in hand. (X is the amount of cards the source of damage has in their hand. Max of 5.)
2. Discard at least X+1 cards, then deal 1 damage to the source of damage. (X is the amount of cards the source of damage has in their hand.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Si Ma Lang</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Selfless Governor

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Manage Army:
At the end of a hero's turn, if the amount of cards in their hand is less than 2, that hero may draw a card and give you all the cards in their hand. Then you give the same number of cards back to that hero.

Rid the Sickness:
Once per a hero's main phase, you may discard X cards and target up to X heros to gain 1 health. If any of the discarded cards were BLACK, you lose 1 health.
(X is the amount of your missing health.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Wen Ping</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Fortified City Veteran

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Town Guardian:
Whenever another hero becomes the only target of an ATTACK or a BLACK tactics card, if their health is less than your health; you may discard a card and choose one:
1. Draw a card, then become the target instead.
2. Cancel the effects of the card. Then return the card back to the hand of the hero who has used it at the end of turn.
(If for some reason you cannot correctly be the target, you must choose option 2. For example, you do not have a weapon equipped and want to be the attacker for a Duress.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhuge Dan</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Expose and Weed the Rebellion

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Meritorious Service:
When another hero dies, gain 1 unit of maximum health and gain 1 health.

Revolt: (Awakening Ability)
At the beginning of your turn, if you are missing health and your maximum health amount is greater than the number of surviving heroes, draw cards until the amount of cards in your hand is equal your maximum health and you gain the [HEAVY] and [COLLAPSE] abilities.

[Heavy]:
Whenever your maximum health amount changes, draw a card.

[Collapse]:
At the end of your turn, if you are not the hero with lowest current health, you must either lose 1 health or lose 1 unit of maximum health.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Wang Ji</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Path to Unification

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Astonishing Control:
During your main phase, whenever you target a hero with a basic or tactics card, you may discard a card from a hero who was not the target; then that hero draws a card.
(Using self targeting cards such as Peach, Wine, or Sleight of Hand would allow you to target any other hero. This skill activates when you play delay tactics cards as well, but not when the delayed effects of performing judgement occur.)

Hasten Advance:
At the end of your turn, you may draw 2 cards; then discard cards from your hand until you have X.
(X is the number of times you've activated ASTONISHING CONTROL this turn.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Wang Lang</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Babbling Pheoniz

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Sharp Tongue:
Once during your main phase, you may clash with up to 3 other target heroes simultaneously. Then the loser of the clash chooses one:
1. The loser discards a card.
2. You draw a card.
		  
If you are the loser of the clash, you gain 1 [RICH TONGUE] token.
(If you are the loser, you choose one of the options and gain a [RICH TONGUE] token.)

Intense Words:
After you reveal your clash card, if your card rank is less than X, you may +X to the rank, if your rank is equal to X, this is treated as you not having activated [SHARP TONGUE] this turn.
(X is the number of [RICH TONGUE] tokens you have.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Li Tong</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Moving Alone Among Ten Thousand

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Push the Front:
Whenever you are dealt damage, for each point of damage you receive, you may attach a card onto your hero as an [EDGE].

At the beginning of your turn, remove all [EDGE] cards attached on your hero and draw X cards twice.
You may play +X additional ATTACKs until the end of turn.
(X is the number of [EDGE] cards removed.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Cao Hong</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Lucky General

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Intervene:
At the end of your turn, you may play an equipment card onto another taget hero's equipment zone.
If the equipment was a weapon, discard a card from a target hero within your physical range.
If the equipment was a armor, the targeted hero draws a card.
If the equipment was a mount, targeted hero gains 1 health
(You cannot replace a equipment from an occupied slot.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Xin Xian Ying</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Prestigiously Wise Noblewoman

Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Loyalty:
Once during your main phase, you may reveal 1 card from your hand, then choose a target hero with a hand size that is greater than their current health to reveal X cards from their hand, where X is the difference between hand cards and current HP. Then compare the revealed cards and apply the following:
1. If at least 1 of the targeted hero's revealed cards has the same color as your card, you draw 1 card from the library or discard 1 card from that hero.
2. If at least 1 of the targeted hero's revealed cards has the same rank as your card, change this ability to "TWICE DURING YOUR TURN".
3. If there are no color or ranks matching, your hand size limit is reduced by 1 for the rest of the game.

(You choose and reveal the cards from the targeted hero's hand.)

Ability and Insight:
At the beginning of your draw phase, you may choose one:
1. Your hand size limit is increased by +1 for the rest of the game; and you cannot play cards targeting other heroes until the end of turn.
2. Gain 1 health and you cannot play cards on yourself until the end of turn.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Ji Kang</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Isolated Serenity in the High Peaks

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Harmonizing Chords:
Whenever you are dealt damage, you may choose to have the source of damage:
1. Lose 1 health and equip a random equipment from the library. (Draw until an equipment is reveal, then return the rest of the cards back and shuffle the library)
2. Gain 1 health and discard 1 equipment.

Whenever you gain health, you may choose another target hero to:
1. Lose 1 health and equip a random equipment from the library. (Draw until an equipment is reveal, then return the rest of the cards back and shuffle the library) 
2. Gain 1 health and discard 1 equipment.

If the equipment card played or discarded was CLUBS suited, you draw a card.

Silence:
When you are dead, you may choose a target hero to randomly gain a ability from [HARMONIZING CHORD MANUSCRIPT]. Until the beginning of that hero's next turn, that hero cannot be the target of CLUBS suited cards.
(Assign a suit to each ability on [HARMONIZING CHORD MANUSCRIPT], then reveal a card from the library to determine the ability being gained.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Harmonizing Chords Manuscript</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Ability:

(Whenever you gain an abiltity from this card, you cannot be targeted by CLUBS suited cards until the beginning of your turn.)

Violent Chord:
Whenever you are dealt damage, you may have the source of damage lose 1 health and equip a random equipment from the library.

Intense Chord:
Whenever you gain health, you may choose another target hero to lose 1 health and equip a random equipment from the library.

Gentle Chord:
Whenever you are dealt damage, you may have the source of damage gain 1 health and discard an equipment.

Harmonious Chord:
Whenever you gain health, you may choose another target hero to gain 1 health and discard an equipment.

(Draw until an equipment is reveal, then return the rest of the cards back and shuffle the library.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Xi Zhi Cai</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Genius that Defies the World

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Heaven's Envy:
Whenever your judgment is resolved, take the judgment result into your hand.

Early Complement:
At the beginning of the game, choose a target hero to be your "Protegee".
Whenever your "Protegee" is dealt damage, you are also dealt the same amount of damage.
Whenever your "Protegee" gains health, you also gain the same amount of health.

Counter Plan:
Whenever you are dealt damage, for each point of damage you receive, you may perform a judgement.
If the judgement result is RED, choose a target hero to draw a card; if the target hero is your "Protegee", that hero draws 2 cards.
If the judgement result is BLACK, you may take a card from another target hero.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhu Ling</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Minister of Gaotang

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Warlike:
Once during your main phase, you may discard a card and lose 1 unit of health.
If your discarded card was a basic card, until the end of turn, you may use basic cards as any basic card.
If your discarded card was a tactics card, you draw 2 cards and ignore any range requirements for cards you play until the end of turn.
If your discarded card was a equipment card, until the end of turn, whenever you target a hero with an ATTACK, the targeted hero must discard 2 cards.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Cao Chun</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Tiger Leopard Rider

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Heavily Armored:
At the beginning of your main phase, you may draw X cards and discard X cards; if any of the discarded cards were from your equipment zone, treat each discarded equipment as you playing an ATTACK to a targeted hero. These ATTACKs ignore any range requirements.
(X is the number of equipment cards you have equipped during this game. Max of 7.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Lu Zhi</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Admiration for Virtue

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Clear Devotion:
During your main phase, you may draw 2 cards, if you do, at the end of your turn, you switch hands with the hero with the lowest amout of cards in their hand.

Defend the Border:
Once during each hero's turn, whenever you need to play a ATTACK or a DODGE in response to an effect, you may announce that you play an ATTACK or DODGE and treat it as so.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Cao Ying</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Blue</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Phoenix Cries over Longcheng 

Health/Gender: 4F

Ability:

Ascend Above Others:
Once during your main phase, after targeting a hero with an ATTACK or tactics card that deals damage, you may choose a targeted hero and make 3 guesses whether the hero has any combination of the 3 card types.
(Your guesses have to be binary, for example: If the targeted hero has a basic card or not. If the targeted hero has a tactics card or not, If the targeted hero has an equipment card or not.)

If 1 of your guesses was correct, the damage you have dealt is increased by +1.
If 2 of your guesses were correct, you draw 2 cards.
If 3 of your guesses were correct, you gain the [VILLAINOUS HERO] and [UNNATURAL DEATH] abilities.

Conceal Inbetween:
At the end of your turn, you may randomly choose a target hero and look at X cards from their hand.
(X is the lowest number of cards a surviving hero has in their hand.)

[Villainous Hero]:
Whenever you are dealt damage by a card effect, you may draw a card from the library or take the card that damaged you into your hand.

[Unnatural Death]:
When a hero dies, you may take all cards owned by that hero into your hand.
(This happens before revealing the role)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
  </CardData>
</CardDataCollection>