<?xml version="1.0" encoding="Windows-1252"?>
<CardDataCollection xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <CardData>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhang Jiao</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: General of the Heavens
      
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Lightning Strike:
Whenever you play or use a DODGE, you may choose another target hero to perform a judgment:
1. If the result is a SPADES suit, you deal 2 LIGHTNING damage to that hero.
2. If the result is a CLUBS suit, you deal 1 LIGHTNING damage to that hero and gain 1 health.

Dark Magic:
Whenever a hero performs a judgement, you may take the judgement card and replace it with a BLACK card from your hand or equipment zone. The judgement is resolved with the new card.

Amber Sky: (Emperor Ability)
Once during the main phase of a KINGDOMLESS faction hero's turn, the KINGDOMLESS faction hero may give you a DODGE or LIGHTNING BOLT card.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Yuan Shao</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: From Noble Heritage 

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Random Strike:
During your main phase, you may discard 2 cards of the same suit from your hand and treat it as you playing HAIL OF ARROWS.

Bloodline:
Your maximum hand size is increase by X, where X is 2 times the number of other surviving KINGDOMLESS faction heroes.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Dong Zhuo</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Devil King

Health/Gender: 8M

Ability:

Drown in Wine:
You may use a SPADES suited card from your hand as WINE.

Garden of Lust:
When a FEMALE hero plays an ATTACK on you, it can only be cancelled by 2 DODGE and vice versa.

Collapse:
At the end of your turn, if you are not the hero with lowest health, you must either lose 1 life or lose 1 unit of max health.

Tyrant: (Emperor Ability)
Whenever another KINGDOMLESS faction hero deals damage, you may have that hero perform a judgement; if the result is BLACK, you gain 1 health.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Yuan Shu</cardName>
	  <portraitOverride>Yuan Shu03</portraitOverride>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Emperor of Zhong

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Extravagant:
During your draw phase, you draw X cards instead.
(X is the number of surviving factions in play.)

During your discard phase, if you have not dealt damage this turn, draw cards until the number of cards in your hand is the same as your current health; if you have more than 1 damage, your hand size this turn is equal to the amount of your missing health.

False Emperor: (Emperor Ability)
Whenever you discard cards during your discard phase, you may give 1 of the discarded cards to each surviving KINGDOMLESS faction hero in turn sequence.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Hua Tuo</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Miracle Physician
      
Health/Gender: 3M
      
Ability:

First Aid:
Outside of your turn, you may play RED cards from your hand and equipment zone as a PEACH.

Book of Green Vesicles:
Once during your main phase, you may discard a card in hand and target a hero, that hero gains 1 health. If the card you discard is RED, you may activate this ability again, but cannot target the same hero.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Lu Bu</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Embodiment of Force
      
Health/Gender: 5M

Ability:

Matchless:
Whenever you are the source of an ATTACK, the defending hero needs to play 2 DODGE cards in order to cancel the ATTACK.
Whenever you are involved in a duel, the other hero needs to discard 2 ATTACK cards in order to respond to your discarded ATTACK.

Mercenary Contract:
Whenever you deal damage to a target hero with an ATTACK, you may take a card from his hand or equipment zone. If the card you take is not an equipment card, the targeted hero draws a card. If the card you take is an equipment card, the targeted hero chooses another target hero and this is treated as you playing a DUEL to the other targeted hero.
(The targeted hero cannot choose themself as the target for the DUEL and must choose another target hero.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Diao Chan</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Unrivalled Dancing Princess 
      
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Wedge Driving:
Once during your main phase, you may discard a card and choose 2 target MALE heroes. If you do, this is treated as one of them playing a DUEL on the other. (You pick which hero initiates the DUEL.)

Eclipse:
At the end of your turn, you may draw a card. If you have no cards in your hand, you may draw 2 cards instead.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Diao Chan</cardName>
	  <portraitOverride>Diao Chan02</portraitOverride>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Masterpiece of Dance and Beauty
      
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Soul Surrender:
Once during your main phase, you may discard a card and flip your hero card; then take all the cards from the hand of a target MALE hero. At the end of you main phase, you must give X cards to the targeted MALE hero.
(X is current health of the targeted MALE hero. You may choose to give cards from your hand or equipment zone. If you have fewer cards than the MALE hero's current health, you must gives him all of your cards.)

Eclipse:
At the end of your turn, you may draw a card. If you have no cards in your hand, you may draw 2 cards instead.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Hua Xiong</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Devil General
      
Health/Gender: 6M

Ability: 

Military Glory:
Whenever you are dealt damage by a RED ATTACK or a ATTACK with WINE, you lose 1 units of max health.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Hua Xiong</cardName>
	  <portraitOverride>Hua Xiong02</portraitOverride>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Dominating Commands
      
Health/Gender: 6M

Ability: 

Swagger:
Whenever a hero deals damage to you with a RED ATTACK, that hero may gain 1 health or draw a card. If the ATTACK was not RED, you draw a card.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Yuan Shu</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Ever Increasing Ambition
      
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Arrogant:
At the beginning of the EMPEROR's turn, you may draw 1 card. If you do, the EMPEROR's hand limit is reduced by -1 until the end of turn.

All in same boat:
Whenever another hero plays an ATTACK and you are within that hero's attack range, if the number of cards in your hand is greater than your current health, that hero can only choose you as the target of any ATTACK.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Yuan Shu</cardName>
	  <portraitOverride>Yuan Shu02</portraitOverride>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Self Declared Emperor
      
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Mediocrity:
During your draw phase, you draw X additional cards.
At the beginning of your discard phase, you discard X cards.
(X is the number of surviving factions in play.)

Pseudo-Emperor:
You gain the Emperor ability of the current EMPEROR.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Yu Ji</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Priest of Tai Ping
      
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Bewilder:
Whenever you want to use a basic or non-delay tactics card, you may play a card face down and announce a basic or non-delay tactics card name you want the face down card to be to played as. Then each hero in sequence states whether the face down card is the same as the announced card named or not. If no hero doubts the face down card, the effects of the announced card proceeds to being resolved. If any heroes doubt the face down card, it is immediately revealed after having asked all heroes in sequence.

If the name of the revealed card is the same as what you have announced, all heroes who have doubted loses 1 health; if the revealed card has a HEARTS suit, resolve the card as the announced name.
If the name of the revealed card is not the same as what you have announced, all heroes who have doubted draws a card; the announced card's effect is canceled and the card is discarded.
(Heroes on the brink of death state cannot doubt you. If the card's effect was canceled through being revealed as false, it is counted as you never having played the announced card at all. For example, if the announced ATTACK was false, you are still allowed to play another ATTACK.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Yu Ji</cardName>
	  <portraitOverride>Yu Ji02</portraitOverride>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Casting Illusion to the Crowds
      
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Bewilder:
Once during each hero's main phase, you may announce a basic or non-delay tactics card name and play a card face down. This card is treated as the announced card.
Before resolving the effects of your announced card, any hero may choose to doubt you and declare that the name of the announced card does not match the name of the card you have played face down; if any hero doubts you, reveal the face down card immediately.
If the name of the revealed card is different from what you have announced, cancel the card's effects and discard it.
If the name of the revealed card is the same as what you have announced, resolve the effects of the card and the hero who doubted you gains the [HAUNTED] ability.

[HAUNTED]:
You cannot doubt cards played by [BEWILDER].
If your health is equal to 1, all your abilities except [HAUNTED] cannot be triggered or activated.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Pang De</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Rider and Ride As One
      
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Horsemanship:
The physical range you see other heroes is reduced by -1.

Fierce Attack:
Whenever you play an ATTACK targeting a hero, you may discard a card from that hero's hand or equipment zone. If the discarded card was an equipment, this ATTACK cannot be cancelled by a DODGE. If the discarded card was not an equipment, that hero take this ATTACK card into their hand.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhao Yun</cardName>
	  <portraitOverride>Zhao Yun02</portraitOverride>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Vanguard on a White Horse
      
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Dragon Courage:
You may play or discard ATTACK cards as DODGE or vice versa.

Pierce the Formation:
Whenever you activate [DRAGON COURAGE], you may immediately take a card from the hand of the targeted hero who made you activate [DRAGON COURAGE].
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Ma Chao</cardName>
	  <portraitOverride>Ma Chao02</portraitOverride>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Eternally A Hero
      
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Pursuit:
The physical range you see heroes with health less than you is 1.

Sworn Revenge:
Your ATTACKs may target up to +X additional heroes.
(X is your missing health.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Yan Liang &amp; Wen Chou</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Tiger and Wolf brothers
      
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Dual Heroes:
At the beginning of your draw phase, you may choose to skip your draw and perform a judgment; reveal the judgment card and take it into your hand. 
Until the end of your turn, you may play cards in your hand with opposite color to the revealed card as a DUEL.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Jia Xu</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Cold-Blooded Advisor

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Perfect Murder:
During your turn, if a hero is on the brink of death; only you and that hero may use PEACH cards.

Upheaval: (Limited Ability)
During your main phase, each hero other than you must choose to play an ATTACK targeting another hero closest in attack range to them or lose 1 health.

Shroud:
You cannot be the target of BLACK tactics cards.
(This includes cards that target all heroes and non-delay tactics cards.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zou Ci</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Mysterious Transcendent

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Incarnation:
At the beginning of the game, you randomly take 2 unused hero cards as [INCARNATION], reveal them and declare one to be active. You only gain 1 ability from the active [INCARNATION]. Your gender and faction become the gender and faction of the [INCARNATION].
(Emperor, Awakening, and Limited Abilities are excluded.)

At the beginning and end of your turn, you may replace your active [INCARNATION] with another one and gain 1 ability from the new active [INCARNATION].

Rebirth:
Whenever you are dealt damage, for each damage, gain 1 random [INCARNATION] from the unused hero cards.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Cai Wen Ji</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Lonely Dame in Foreign Lands
      
Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Song of Lament:
Whenever a hero is dealt damage by an ATTACK, you may discard a card from your hand or equipment zone and perform a judgment and activate the effect relating to the suit below:

HEARTS: The defender gains 1 life.
DIAMONDS: The defender draws 2 cards.
CLUBS: The source of damage discards 2 cards.
SPADES: The source of damage flip their hero card.

Sorrow:
The hero who killed you loses all abilities for the rest of the game.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Gao Shun</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Ever-Victorious Warrior
      
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Fearless Charge:
Once during your main phase, you may clash with a target hero; if you win, until end of your turn, you ignore the effects of any armor equipment on that hero, ignore any attack/physical range requirements for cards you play targeting that hero, and you may play any number of ATTACK cards targeting that hero.
If you did not win, you cannot play ATTACK cards until the end of your turn.

Prohibition:
Your WINE cards are always treated as ATTACKs.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Chen Gong</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Upright and Heroic
      
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Brilliant Scheme:
Once during yout main phase, you may give 1 equipment card or ATTACK card to a target hero, that hero then chooses one of the following:
1. The targeted hero choooses a hero within their attack range and is considered to have used an ATTACK.
2. The targeted hero draws a card.

Late Response:
Whenever you are dealt damage outside of your turn, you ignore all effects from ATTACK and non-delay tactics card until the end of this turn.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Liu Biao</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Ruler of Jiang Nan
      
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Self-Preservation:
During your draw phase, you may draw X additional cards. If you do, cards you play this turn cannot target other heroes.
(X is the number of factions in play. You cannot use cards that target all other heroes, but if you use cards that target all heroes, you will be the only hero targeted instead.)

House of Royalty:
Your hand size is increased by X. 
(X is the number of surviving factions in play.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Pang Tong</cardName>
	    <portraitOverride>Pang Tong02</portraitOverride>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Lofty Man of Jiang Chu
      
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Screw Work:
Whenever you gain cards in your hand outside of your turn, you must discards those cards.
During your turn, whenever you discard a card that shares the same rank as a card in the discard pile, you may take the card that shares the same rank into your hand.
(You should never be able to gain cards outside of your turn. Delay tactics and equipment cards that are moved into your field are not required to be discarded.)

Inebriated: (Limited ability)
Once per game, at the beginning of your turn, you reveal 3 cards from top of the deck and attach them onto your hero. You cannot play or be affected by the same type of cards attached onto your hero.
At the beginning of each of your turns, you reveal another 3 cards attach them onto your hero. This process continues until you have 2 cards of the same rank. 
Whenever you have 2 cards of the same rank attached onto your hero, take all the attached cards into your hand.
(Cards that you gain from this ability is not affected by [SCREW WORK].)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Gan Ning</cardName>
	  <portraitOverride>Gan Ning02</portraitOverride>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Feathered and Belled Warrior
      
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Silver Bells:
During your main phase, you may discard a BLACK card; then take a card from another target hero and attach it onto your hero face up as a [BROCADE]. You may have a max of 4 [BROCADES] attached.

Military Prestige:
At the end of your turn, you may discard 3 [BROCADES] and choose a target hero, the targeted hero chooses one:
1. The targeted hero gives you a DODGE, then you give the DODGE to another target hero.
2. The targeted hero loses 1 health; then you may choose one of their equipment in their equipment zone and attach it face down onto their hero. The attached card is put back into their equipment zone at the end of their next turn.
(The faced down card cannot be affected by other card affects while attached to the target hero.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Empress Fu</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Stand Aloof From Affairs
      
Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Anxious Fear:
At the beginning of each other hero's turn, if you are damaged, you may clash with the current turn hero.
If you win, that hero may only play cards that target themself until the end of turn.
If you lose, the physical range between the both of you is considered 1 until end of turn.

Plead for Help:
Whenever you become the target of an ATTACK, you may choose a target hero other than the attacker. The targeted hero may give you a DODGE card. If the targeted hero does not, they become the additional target of the ATTACK.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Li Ru</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Demonic Advisor
      
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Annihilate: 
At the end of your turn, you may deal 1 damage to a target hero (other than you) with no cards in hand.

Exterminate: 
Once during your main phase, you may put one BLACK tactics card on top of the library and target a hero with cards in their hand, that hero must either discards a tactics card, or discard 2 cards from his hand or equipment zone.

Burn the City: (Limited ability)
During your main phase, you may target each other hero. Each targeted hero in sequence must choose one of the following:
1. Discard 1+X cards from hand or equipment zone. (X is the number of cards the previous player has discarded.)
2. You deal 2 FIRE damage to the targeted hero.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Ju Shou</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Military Schemer
      
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Progressive Strategy:
Whenever you play a card during your main phase, if the card you play has the same rank or suit as the previous card you have played this turn, you may draw a card.

Aiming the North:
Whenever you are dealt damage, if it was the first time you are dealt damage this turn, you gain 1 health; if it was not the first time you are dealt damage this turn, you lose 1 health.
(This effect activates before you enter the brink of death state.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Lady Cai</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Queen of Jin Zhou
      
Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Eavesdrop:
At the end of each other hero's turn, if they have not played a card that targeted a hero other than themself this turn, you may choose one of the following:
1. You take a card in that hero's equipment zone into your equipment zone. (You cannot replace a equipment from an occupied slot)
2. You draw a card.
(This can be activated even if that hero only played cards that target all heroes.)

Cession: (Limited Ability)
During your main phase, you may give all cards in your equipment zone to another target hero, that hero chooses one of the following:
1. You gain X health.
2. You deal 1 damage to X target heroes within that hero's attack range.
(X is the number of cards you chose to give to that hero.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Gong Sun Yuan</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Shady Warlord
      
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Disloyalty: 
Once during your main phase, you may reveal all cards in your hand. If all your cards are not the same color, you discard all cards of one color, then choose X target heroes and take a card from each of their hand or equipment zone into your hand.
(X is the number of cards you discarded.)

If you put 2 or more cards into your hand, you lose 1 health.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Guo Tu &amp; Feng Ji</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Ferocious Dual
      
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Reckless Assault:
At the beginning of your main phase, you may draw 2 cards. If you do, your hand size limit becomes X this turn.
(X is the amount of damage you deal this turn.)

Cover Up:
Whenever you need to play a DODGE, you may choose to let the current turn hero draw a card; if that hero is not among heroes with the highest number of cards in hand, you discard a card from the hero who has the highest number of cards in their hand and treat this as you using a DODGE.
(If there is a draw among heroes with the highest amount of cards in hand, you may choose one of them to discard from.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Liu Yu</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Benevolent Ruler
      
Health/Gender: 2M

Ability:

Peacekeeping:
Once per each hero's main phase, if the number of cards in your hand is greater than your current health, you may target a hero with you in their attack range; unless that hero plays an ATTACK targeting you, that hero gives you an equipment card from their equipment zone to your hand.

Ancestral Blessing:
At the beginning of the game, you increase your max health by X.
If all heroes of a faction are removed from the game, you reduce your max health by -1.
(X is the number of surviving factions in the game.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhang Rang</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Powerful Eunuch
      
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Creating Chaos:
You may announce a basic card or non-delay tactics card name, then play a card from your hand as the announced card. You cannot announce a card name you have already used with [CREATING CHAOS] during this game. After the announced card's effect is resolved, you target another hero and that hero chooses one of the following:
1. The targeted hero gives you a card from their hand or equipment zone which is not the same type as the announced card.
2. You lose 1 health and cannot use [CREATING CHAOS] for the rest of the turn.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Gong Sun Zan</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The White Horse General
      
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Fierce Mount:
Whenever you deal damage to a target hero with a BLACK ATTACK, you may discard a card from their equipment zone; if the discarded card is a mount, you take it into your hand.

Follower of Virtue:
Whenever you have 3 or more health, the physical range you see other heroes is reduced by -1.
Whenever you have 2 or less health, the physical range other heroes see you is increased by +1.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhang Lu</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Spreading Aid Throughout the Nation
      
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Free Accomondation: 
At the end of your turn, if you do not have any [RICE] cards attached to you, you may draw 2 cards and attach 2 cards from your hand or equipment zone onto your character face-up as [RICE] cards. When the last [RICE] card is removed from you, you gain 1 health.

Donate: 
When you deal or are dealt damage, the hero who was dealt damage may put a [RICE] card into their hand per damage received.

Rice Religion:
When a player performs a judgment, you may replace the revealed judgement card with a [RICE] card. The new card becomes the judgment result.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Cai Yong</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Great Graceful Scholar
      
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Discourse in Praise:
Whenever you play or become the target of another hero's SPADES suited card, you may take a card from the top of the library and attach it to your hero as a [BOOK]. (max. 4)
Each [BOOK] card increases your hand size limit by +1.

Extensive Communication:
At the end of your draw phase, you may swap any number of [BOOK] cards with the cards you own. If your [BOOKS] cards are one each suit, give all your [BOOK] cards to another target hero.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Cao Jie</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Empress Xianmu of Han
      
Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Protect the Seal:
Whenever you become the target of an ATTACK, you may announce the name of a card. Unless the attacker discards the card you announced and takes 1 card from your hand or equipment zone, the ATTACK is cancelled.
(You may only announce each card name once per game.)

Benifiting Civilians:
At the end of your turn, you may draw X cards.
(X is the number of players who has less cards in hand than their current health.)
Then you reveal X cards from your hand and select a target hero. Starting from that hero, each other hero in sequence takes 1 of the revealed cards.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Ling Ju</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Love's Dying Dream
      
Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Deplete Karma:
Whenever you deal damage to another hero, if their health is greater than your health, you may discard a BLACK card to increase the damage by +1.
Whenever you are dealt damage by another hero, if their health is greater than your health, you may discard a RED card to reduce the damage by -1.
(This effect takes priority before calculating armor effects.)

Burning Heart:
Whenever another hero dies and reveals their role:
If their role was LOYALIST, you ignore the health requirement when using [DEPLETE KARMA] to reduce damage.
If their role was REBEL, you ignore the health requirement when using [DEPLETE KARMA] to increase damage.
If their role was SPY, you ignore the color requirement when using [DEPLETE KARMA] to reduce damage.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Liu Xie</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Imprisoned Emperor
      
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Mandate of Heaven:
Whenever you become the target of an ATTACK, you may discard 2 cards; then draw 2 cards. A hero, other than you, with the highest amount of health may also perform this skill.
(If you have less than 2 cards, you may discard your hand to activate this skill.)

Secret Edict:
Once per a hero's main phase, you may give all the cards in your hand to a target player; then choose another target hero, the targeted heroes must perform a clash. The winner of the clash is considered to have played an ATTACK on the loser.
(If the seconds targeted hero is unable to perform a clash, the first targeted hero still receives the cards you give. If the clash ends in a draw, nothing happens.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Liu Xie</cardName>
	  <portraitOverride>Liu Xie02</portraitOverride>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Emperor Xian of Han
      
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Royal Grace:
Whenever a tactics card that targets multiple heroes is played, you may choose a target hero and cancel the effect of the tactics card for the targeted hero, then the targeted hero draws a card.

Revive the Han:
At the end of your discard phase, you may attach the discarded cards onto your hero as [IMPERIAL EDICTS].
At the beginning of your turn, you may discard a [IMPERIAL EDICT] and choose to gain one of the following Emperor Abilities until the beginning of your next turn:
1. [ESCORT]
2. [ROUSE]
3. [RESCUED]
4. [BLOODLINE]

You ignore any faction requirements for any of the Emperor Abilities.
(You may only gain one Emperor Ability a turn.)

[Escort]:
Whenever you need to play or discard a DODGE, you may ask each WEI faction hero to play or discard a DODGE for you, then it is treated as you playing the DODGE.

[Rouse]:
Whenever you need to play or discard an ATTACK, you may ask each other SHU faction hero to play or discard an ATTACK for you, then its treated as you playing the ATTACK.
(You cannot use this ability to activate the effect on HEAVEN HALBERD when you have no cards in your hand.)

[Rescued]:
Whenever you are on the brink of death and a WU faction hero uses a PEACH on you, you gain 2 health instead of 1.

[Bloodline]:
Your maximum hand size is increase by X, where X is 2 times the number of other surviving KINGDOMLESS faction heroes.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhang Bao</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: General of the Land
      
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Curse:
Once per a hero's main phase, you may attach a card from your hand as a [CURSE] onto another target hero with no [CURSE] card attached.
When a hero with a [CURSE] card attach performs a judgement, the [CURSE] card is used as the judgement result. At the end of a hero's turn, any hero who used a [CURSE] as their judgement result loses 1 health.
(No card is flipped from the library when performing a judgement for the hero with a [CURSE] attached, the [CURSE] card is immediately used as the judgement result. When you are dead, the attached [CURSE] card effects remain in play.

Shadow Soldier:
When a hero with a [CURSE] card attached plays a card with the same suit as the [CURSE], you draw a card. If you draw 2 cards due to the effect of the same [CURSE] card, the [CURSE] card is remove from that hero.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>    
    <Card>
      <cardName>Fu Wan</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Deep Resolve for the Country
      
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Plan for Defeat:
Whenever you play an ATTACK on a target hero, you may choose one:
1. Draw a card.
2. Discard 1 card from the targeted hero's hand.
If the targeted hero plays a DODGE, the targeted hero discards a card from you.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>    
    <Card>
      <cardName>He Tai Hou</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Vicious and Manipulate Power for Personal Gain
      
Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Poison Wine:
At the beginning of another hero's main phase, you may discard a card from your hand. This is considered as the active hero playing a WINE; then you deal 1 damage to that hero.

Confusing Sorrow:
At the end of each hero's turn, you may draw 3 cards for each hero you have killed this turn.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>    
    <Card>
      <cardName>Yellow Turban Rebels</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Thunder Festival Beauties
      
Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Mark of the Sea:
Whenever you play an ATTACK, you may treat it as a LIGHTNING ATTACK.

Sacrifice Offering:
Whenever a hero is being dealt LIGHTNING damage, you may have that hero perform a judgement. If the result is BLACK, the LIGHTNING damage is increased by +1; if the result is RED, the targeted hero takes the judgement card.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>    
    <Card>
      <cardName>Pan Feng</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Coalition Admiral
      
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Mad Axe:
Whenever your ATTACK deals damage to a target hero, you may choose one:
1. Move an equipment card from their equipment zone to your equipment zone.
2. Discard a card from the targeted hero's equipment zone.
(You cannot move an equipment into an occupied equipment zone.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>    
    <Card>
      <cardName>Shi Xie</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: A Formidable Southern Leader
      
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Seek Refudge from War:
At the beginning of your draw phase, if you are at 1 physical range with another hero, you may skip your draw phase. If you do, your physical range with other heroes is increased by +X.
(X is the number of factions in play. The change in physical range is permanent for the rest of the game.)

Under Ritual:
At the end of another hero's turn, if you are not within the attack range of that hero, you may choose one:
1. You draw a card.
2. The target hero draws a card.
Then decrease your physical range with other heroes by 1.
(The change in physical range is permanent for the rest of the game.) 
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Wu Tugu</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Fire Does Not Invade
      
Health/Gender: 15M

Ability:

Burning in War:
Whenever you are dealt FIRE damage, you gain a [BURN] token.
At the end of your turn, you lose X health.
(X is the number of [BURN] tokens you have.)

Fierce and Valiant:
Whenever you play HAIL OF ARROWS or BARBARIAN ASSAULT, if you current health is less than the number of the current round; you may increase the damage by +1.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Huang Yue Ying</cardName>
	  <portraitOverride>Huang Yue Ying02</portraitOverride>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Diamond in the Rough
      
Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Ingenious:
At the beginning of your main phase, you may discard any number of equipment cards; then reveal X cards from the deck. Take any revealed tactics cards.
(X is double the amount of equipment cards you have discarded.)

Exquisite:
If you do not have any armor equipped, you are considered to have EIGHT TRIGRAMS equipped.
If you do not have any mounts equipped, your hand size limit is increased by +1.
If you do not have any treasure equipped, you have [WONDROUS TALENT].

[Wondrous Talent]:
All tactics card you play may ignore any range requirements. Your equipped armor cannot be removed unless the targeted hero is within physical range of you.
(Remove meaning that your armor card will no longer be in your equipment zone.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhao Yun</cardName>
	  <portraitOverride>Zhao Yun03</portraitOverride>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Swimming Dragon of Changshan
      
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Deep Love to Motherland:
You may play DIAMOND suited cards as ATTACKs or DODGEs.
During your main phase, ATTACKs you play may target all heroes within your attack range.

Benevolence: (Limited Ability)
Once per game, you may loose the [FOLLOWER OF VIRTUE] ability, increase your max health by +1, gain 1 health, and choose a target hero to draw 3 cards.

Follower of Virtue:
Whenever you have 3 or more health, the physical range you see other heroes is reduced by -1.
Whenever you have 2 or less health, the physical range other heroes see you is increased by +1.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Ma Chao</cardName>
	  <portraitOverride>Ma Chao03</portraitOverride>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Ferocious Lion of the West
      
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Pursuit:
The physical range you see heroes with health less than you is 1.

Acacia:
At the beginning of your main phase, you may reveal the cards in your hand; if you do not have any ATTACK cards in your hand, you may play ATTACKs without playing the card until the number of cards in your hand changes.
(To play an ATTACK with this ability, you must choose a target hero and annouce the ATTACK. You do not play a card, but the targeted hero may still respond to your ATTACK. This ATTACK counts towards the ATTACK restriction limit. ATTACK restriction limit: A hero is limted to playing 1 ATTACK per main phase unless another effect says otherwise.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Dong Bai</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Granddaughter of Dong Zhuo 
      
Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Punish:
Once during each hero's main phase, you may reveal a card from your hand and give it to another target hero. If the card is BLACK, the target hero chooses one:
1. Target hero discards 2 cards.
2. You draw 2 cards.

Crafty:
Your black cards do not count towards you max hand size limit. BLACK cards you give to other heroes cannot be played or discarded unless their health decreases.
(The hero must lose health or take damage before being able to use BLACK cards given or taken from you. Cards taken from you by any card effects or abilities are still under the effects of this ability.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Ta Dun</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Northern Barbarian King
      
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Armed Upheaval:
Your ATTACKs and BLACK non-delay tactics cards can target +X additional heroes.
Whenever your ATTACK or BLACK non-delay tactics card targets any heroes, if the number of targets is less than X; X is reduced to 0.
(X is the number of times you've dealt damage.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Yan Bai Hu</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: White Tiger of Dong Wu
      
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Robbery:
During your action phase, the first time you deal damage to another hero, you take a card from each equipment zone and judgement zone of that target hero. You cannot target any other heroes until the end of the turn.
(You are only able to target yourself after activating this ability. This ability does not activate if you kill the hero you are targeting or when targeting a hero with no equipment or judgement cards in play for you to take.)

Lodge:
Whenever another hero becomes the target of a RED basic or non-delay tactics card, if you are within 1 physical range of that hero and you are not the source of the card being played; you also become the target of the card.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Qu Yi</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: A Righteous Charge Through the Boundary Bridge
      
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Concealed Horserider:
Heroes within a range of 1 to you cannot play cards in response to the cards you play.

Arrogant and Unrestraint:
If you are the hero with the highest number of cards in your hand, the damage you deal and the damage you receive is increased by +1.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Wang Yun</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Minister of the Interior
      
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Continuios Calculations:
Once during each hero's main phase, you may give an ATTACK or a BLACK tactics card to another target hero; the target hero equips a random weapon from the library and then chooses one:
1. The targeted hero uses the given card on another hero, then the targeted hero gives their equipped weapon to one of the heroes that were targeted by the used card.
2. Treat this as you using the given card on the targeted hero, then the targeted hero gives you the weapon.
(Both you and the targeted hero must be able to completely fullfill either options, cards that cannot completely fullfill the options are illegal to use with this ability. Cards that are illegal to use are BARBARIAN ASSAULT, IMPECCABLE PLAN, and LIGHTNING BOLT. Cards that are potentially illegal due to some restrictions are ATTACK, DURESS, and RATIONS DEPLETED.)

Carry Out Scheme: (Awakening Ability)
Whenever another hero has accumulatively dealt 3 or more damage by using cards received from [CONTINUIOUS CALCULATIONS], you lose the [CONTINUIOUS CALCULATIONS] ability and gain the [BOAST] ability.

[Boast]:
Once during your main phase, you may play 1 equipment or ATTACK as a random tactics card. At the end of the turn, if you did not deal damage, you lose 1 health.
Roll a 20-sided dice to see which tactics card is randomly chosen:
1. BARARIAN ASSAULT
2. HAIL OF ARROWS
3. OATH OF PEACH GARDEN
4. HARVEST
5. SLEIGHT OF HAND
6. IMPECCABLE PLAN
7. BURN BRIDGES
8. DURESS
9. DUEL
10. PILFER
11. BLAZE
12. IRON CHAINS
13. ACEDIA
14. LIGHTNING BOLT
15. RATIONS DEPLETED
16. HIDDEN INTENTIONS
17. SEDUCTIVE RUSE
18+. Re-roll

(The color, rank and suit of the tactics card being played is the same as the equipment or ATTACK card used to activate this ability.)

Note: Wang Yun has 2 new tactics cards that can only be used under his possession, HIDDEN INTENTIONS and SEDUCTIVE RUSE. You may only be able to use these tactics cards through activating his [BOAST] ability.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Bei Mi Kou Hu</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Queen of Wa Friendly to Wei
      
Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Release Puppet:
At the beginning of each round, a hero other than you with the lowest current health gains a [PUPPET] attached to their hero unless they already have a [PUPPET] attached.
At the beginning of you turn, you may choose a target hero that does not have a [PUPPET] attached, then attach a [PUPPET] onto the targeted hero.

Bone Cut:
Whenever a hero with a [PUPPET] is dealt damage, you draw a card.

False Worship: (Awakening Ability)
At the beginning of your turn, if you have gained 7 or more cards from your [BONE CUT] ability, increase your max health by +1 and gain 1 health. The attach a [PUPPET] onto each hero who does not already have a [PUPPET] attached. You lose the [BONE CUT] ability and gain the [PUPPET MASTER] ability.

[Puppet Master]:
Whenever you become the only target of a basic or non-delay tactics cards played by a hero with a [PUPPET] attached, you may remove the [PUPPET] from that hero and cancel the card effect.
Whenever you play a basic or non-delay tactics card that only targets a hero, you may remove a [PUPPET] from another target hero and have that hero be an additional target.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Liu Qi</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Arise from the Summer of Zhenjiang
      
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Ruse:
At the beginning of your main phase, you may choose a target hero to reveal and give you a card. Until the end of turn, all other heroes may not respond to cards you play with the revealed card.

Stationed By the River:
At the end of your turn, if you did not skip your main phase and did not play any cards targeting other heroes during your main phase, you may draw X cards.
(X is the number of surviving factions in play.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Han Ba</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Demon that Brings Droughts
      
Health/Gender: 4F

Ability:

Burning Sky:
At the end if your turn, if the number of cards in your hand is less than your current health, you may choose a target hero within your attack range and take a card from their hand, then attach it onto your hero as a [BURNT] token. Your attack range is increased by X.
(X is the number of [BURNT] tokens attached onto your hero.)

Broiling Day: (Awakaneing Ability)
Whenever you have 3 or more [BURNT] tokens, you gain the [BURNING HEART] ability.

Burning Heart:
Once during your main phase, you may discard 2 [BURNT] tokens and choose a target hero, the targeted hero loses 1 health.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Tao Qian</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Held with a Tender Belevolence
      
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Beckoning Misfortune:
Whenever a hero enters the brink of death, your max health becomes 1. Whenever you lose 1 max health, you draw a card.

Moral Aid:
Once per each hero's main phase, whenever you become the target of a card played by a hero, if the that hero's current health is greater than your current health, you may randomly take a basic card that you do not have in your hand from the deck.

Welcoming Offer:
During your main phase, you may give all your non-basic cards from your hand to a target hero with max health greater than you max health; the amount of your max health becomes the same amount of max health of the targeted hero, then gain X health.
(X is the types of cards you gave to the target hero.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Huang Fu Song</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Ambitions to Clear the Frost
      
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Cleaving Axe:
You may use this ability X times during your main phase. Choose a target hero to clash with, if you win, you choose one:
1. The targeted hero cannot play cards from their hand until the end of turn.
2. You may treat this as playing an ATTACK, this ATTACK does not count towards the ATTACK restriction limit.

If you lose the clash, you proceed to end your turn.
(X is the number of surviving Loyalists in the game.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhang Liang</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: General of the People
      
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Call to Arms:
During your main phase, whenever you equip a weapon or play a card that targets yourself, you may perform a judgement.
Then attach the judgement result to your hero as a [SQAURE].
(Non-delay tactics cards that are considered to target yourself would be SLEIGHT OF HAND, HARVEST, and OATH OF PEACH GARDEN. IRON CHAINS and DURESS could also be self targeting if the conditions are met.)

Unifying Power:
At the end of your turn, you may discard a card and/or discard any number of [SQUARE] cards. If the sum of all the discarded cards is 36, you choose a target hero to deal 3 LIGHTNING damage to.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>He Jin</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Outwardly Strength Inwardly Weak
      
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Punishment Scheme:
Once during your main phase, you may target another hero with cards in their hand to give you a card from their hand. If the number of cards in the targeted hero's hand is less than the number of cards in your hand, the targeted hero chooses one of the following:
1. The targeted hero is considered to play an ATTACK targeting you.
2. The targeted hero is considered to play a DUEL targeting you.
(The DUEL that the targeted hero is considered to play can still be cancelled with an IMPECCABLE PLAN.)

Buying Time:
When you are dead, you may choose a target hero and discard X cards from the targeted hero. X is the number of cards you had in your hand and equipment zone.
(You choose which cards to discard from the targeted hero. Cards that are attached to your hero or to your equipment do not count towards X.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Han Sui</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Forcefully Occupying the West
      
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Countering Chaos:
At the end of another hero's turn, if the target hero has more current health than you, or has played an ATTACK targeting you this turn, you may discard a BLACK card and treat it as an ATTACK towards that hero.

Horsemanship:
The physical range you see other heroes is reduced by +1.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Lu Zhi</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Pillar of Han
      
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Excellent Mentor:
At the beginning of the game, you draw a card and then attach a card face up from your hand onto you hero as a [MISSION]. At the end of your turn, you may swap a card from your hand with the [MISSION] card.

Faithful and Honest: (Transform Ability)
(Mode 1):
Once during your main phase, you may target another hero within your attack range, then discard X cards with the same color as the [MISSION] card to deal 1 damage to the targeted hero.
(X is the difference between your current health and the targeted hero's current health.)

(Mode 2):
Outside of your turn, whenever a card you use is put into the discard pile, if the card shares the same type as the [MISSION] card, you may choose a target her to draw a card.

Note: Transform abilities alternate between each mode when activated. You may only first activate the effect of Mode 1 and then activate Mode 2 the next time you choose to use the same ability. You cannot activate the effect from the same mode before choosing to activate the other one first.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Pang De Gong</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Universally Virtuous
      
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Evaluate Talents:
Once during your main phase, you may perform a judgement and activate the effect of the relating suit below:

[Hidden Dragon]: SPADES
Choose a target hero and deal 1 FIRE damage to the targeted hero. If Zhuge Liang is present in the game, you deal 1 damage to 2 target heroes instead.

[Phoenix Chick]: CLUBS
Choose 3 target heroes, the targeted heroes become chained. If Pang Tong is present in the game, you choose 4 target heroes to be chained instead.

[Water Mirror]: HEARTS
Choose a target hero and move an armor card from their equipment zone to another hero's unoccupied equipment zone. If Si Ma Hui is present in game, you move any equipment card from the targeted hero to another hero's unoccupied equipment zone instead.

[Mystic Sword]: DIAMONDS
Choose a target hero to draw a card and gain 1 health. If Xu Shu is present in the game, you draw a card.

Concealed Life:
You ignore all affects from delay tactics cards that affect your draw phase, main phase, or discard phase.
(The delay tactics card may still be played on you, but you do not perform the judgement or it's effects once activated.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Mi Heng</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Hawk that Pecks the Phoenix
      
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Madness:
At the beginning of your main phase, you may perform a judgement. Cards that share the same suit as the judgement result ignore any range restrictions and any limit restrictions; if you play a card that shares the same suit as the judgement result, you may draw a card.
(You may draw up to a max of 5 cards per turn with this ability. Ignoring limit restrictions means you may also ignore the ATTACK restriction limit rule and any rulings that only allow you to play any cards once per turn or main phase.)

Sharp Tongue:
At the end of your discard phase, if the cards you've discarded all have different suits, you may discard a card from another target hero.
(You must discard more than 1 card during your discard phase to activate this ability.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Si Ma Hui</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Mister Water Mirror
      
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Heroic Sacrifice:
At the beginning of the game, you choose 2 target heroes and attach a [DRAGON SEAL] and [PHOENIX SEAL] token to each of the targeted heroes.
Once during your main phase or whenever a hero with a [DRAGON SEAL] or [PHOENIX SEAL] token dies; choose another hero to attach the token onto.
(You may choose not to attach the token to a new hero and have it be discarded upon a hero's death.)

Good Balance:
Whenever a target hero is dealt elemental damage, if the targeted hero is in the chained state and is the starting point for the chain damage, you may view X cards from the top of the library and give them to any number of heroes.
(X is the number of heroes who were chained.)

Hermit:
Whenever you are dealt elemental damage from an ATTACK or tactics card, if you do not have armor equipped or have the [DRAGON SEAL] or [PHOENIX SEAL] attached, the damage is prevented.

[Dragon Seal]:
Whenever a target hero has the [DRAGON SEAL] attached, the targeted hero may use a RED colored card from their hand as a BLAZE.
(You may only use this ability 3 times a round.)

[Phoenix Seal]:
Whenever a target hero has the [PHOENIX SEAL] attached, during their main phase, the targeted hero may use a CLUBS suited card from their hand as IRON CHAINS; or recast that card.
(You may only use this ability 3 times a round.)

[Dragon Phoenix Seal Completion]:
Whenever both the [DRAGON SEAL] and [PHOENIX SEAL] are discarded, you gain the [SEARING HEAT] ability.

[Searing Heat]: (Limited Ability)
Once per game, during your main Phase, you may choose up to 3 target heroes and deal 3 FIRE damage among them. If you deal more than 1 damage to a targeted hero, you discard 1 card of each suit and lose 3 health.
(You must discard as many different suits as you are able to.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zou Shi</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Enchanting Demon
      
Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Source of Calamity:
At the beginning of your turn, you may discard a card and choose to gain an ability from any surviving hero until the beginning of your next turn.
(You cannot gain Emperor abilities, Awakening abilities, or Limited abilities.) 

Allure:
At the end of your turn, you may flip your hero card face down and choose a target hero, then targeted hero flips their hero card.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Kong Rong</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Awe Inspiring Righteousness
      
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Famed Scholar:
Whenever you are dealt damage, the source of damage must show their hand; if the source of damage does not, the damage is reduced by -1.

Courtesy:
Whenever you discard cards, you may choose another target hero and give all the discarded cards to the targeted hero.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Tian Feng</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Marvelous Hero of Hebei
      
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Admonishing at Death's Door:
Whenever you enter the brink of death, you may choose a target hero and choose one of the following:
1. The targeted hero discards X cards, where X is their current health.
2. The targeted hero draws X cards, where X is their missing health.
(You may only activate this ability before using a Peach or asking other heroes to use a Peach for you.)

Following the Trend:
Whenever another hero loses health, if their current health is greater than or equal to the number of cards in your hand, you draw a card.
Whenever a hero dies, you lose 1 health.  
(This ability does not trigger when a hero gains health, then has their current health becomes greater than or equal to the number of cards in your hand.) 
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Ji Ling</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Commander in Chief
      
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Double Edged:
At the beginning of your main phase, you may clash with a target hero. If you win the clash, you may choose a target hero and treat this as you playing an ATTACK to the targeted hero.
If he lose the clash, you proceed to end your main phase.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Ma Teng</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Colorless</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Cavalryman from the West
      
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Horsemanship:
The physical range you see other heroes is reduced by -1.

Rally: (Limited ability)
Once per game, you may choose any number of target heroes. Each targeted hero draws 3 cards. If you were the only hero targeted, you gain 1 health.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
	</CardData>
</CardDataCollection>