<?xml version="1.0" encoding="Windows-1252"?>
<CardDataCollection xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <CardData>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Lu Meng</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>God</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Minister with Divine Enlightment

Health/Gender:3M

Ability:

Look Through:
At the beginning of your draw phase, you may skip your draw phase to reveal 5 cards from the top of the deck, then take 1 card of each suit.

Strike at the Heart:
Once during your main phase, you may choose another target hero and look at the cards in their hand, then reveal a HEARTS suited card and choose one:
1. Discard the HEARTS suited card.
2. Place the card on top of the deck.
(When resolving this ability with Xiao Qiao, any SPADES suited cards can be selected as HEARTS suited card due to her [YOUTHFUL BEAUTY] ability.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Guan Yu</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>God</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Divinity of War

Health/Gender: 5M

Ability:

God of War:
Your HEARTS suited cards are always treated as ATTACKs that ignore any range requirements. 

Warrior Spirit:
Whenever you are dealt damage, the source of damage gains a [NIGHTMARE] token.
When you die, all heroes must perform a judgement. If the judgement result is not a PEACH or OATH OF PEACH GARDEN, that hero dies immediately.
(Any hero who dies by this ability does not go into the brink of death state and is not able to use any card effects to gain health or revive.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhao Yun</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>God</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Aura of the Dragon

Health/Gender: 2M

Ability:

Adversity:
During your draw phase, you draw 2+X additional cards.
(X is your missing health.)

Your hand size limit is increased by 2.

Soul of the Dragon:
You may use X cards with the specific suit as the following:
HEARTS can be used as PEACH.
DIAMONDS can be used as FIRE ATTACK.
CLUBS can be used as DODGE.
SPADES can be used as IMPECCABLE PLAN.
(X is your current health.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Si Ma Yi</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>God</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Founder of the Jin Empire

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Restraint:
Whenever you are dealt 1 damage or discard a card in your discard phase, you gain 1 [RESTRAINT] token.

Promotion: (Awakening Ability)
At the beginning of your turn, if you have 4 or more [RESTRAINT] tokens, decrease your max health by -1 and gain the [EXTREME TACTICS] ability.

[Extreme Tactics]:
You may discard a [RESTRAINT] token to gain a following ability:
1. [DEMONIC TALENT]
2. [BALANCE OF POWER]
3. [GATHERING WISDONM]
4. [BANISH TO EXILE]
5. [PERFECT MURDER]

Breaking Links:
Whenever you kill 1 or more heroes, you take an extra turn immediately at the end of your turn.
(You only gain an extra turn even if you killed more than 1 hero during your turn. If you kill another hero during your extra turn, you would trigger this ability again.)

[Demonic Talent]:
Whenever a hero performs a judgement, you may replace the judgement card with a card from your hand. The judgement is resolved with the new card.
(You do not take the initial judgement card into you hand.)

[Balance of Power]:
Once during your main phase, you may discard any number of cards from your hand and equipment zone; then draw that same amount of cards.

[Gathering Wisdom]:
Whenever you play a tactics card, you may reveal the top card of the library. If it is not a basic card, you take the revealed card. If it is a basic, you may discard a card from your hand and then take the revealed card.

[Banish to Exile]:
Whenever you are dealt damage, you may have target hero flip their hero card. If you do, that hero draw X cards.
(X is your missing health)

[Perfect Murder]:
During your turn, if a hero is on the brink of death; only you and that hero may use PEACH cards.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhuge Liang</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>God</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Sorcerer at the Red Cliffs

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

The Seven Stars:
At the beginning of the game, you draw 11 cards. Then you pick 4 of them to be your starting hand and attach the remaining 7 onto your hero, face-down as [STARS].
At the end of your draw phases, you can swap any number of cards from your hand with the attached [STARS].

Strong Gale:
At the end of your turn, you may discard a [STAR] and choose a target hero. Until the beginning of your next turn, all FIRE damage dealt to that hero is increased by +1.

Heavy Shroud:
At the end of your turn, you may discard any number of [STARS] and choose X target heroes. Until the beginning of your next turn, all damage except LIHGNTING damage is prevented for the targeted heroes.
(X is the number of discarded [STARS].)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhou Yu</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>God</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The God of Fire at the Red Cliffs

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

The Sound of Music:
During your discard phase, if you discard 2 or more cards, you may have each hero gain or lose 1 health.
(This ability targets yourself as well.)

Searing Heat: (Limited Ability)
During your main Phase, you may choose up to 3 target heroes and deal 3 FIRE damage among them. If you deal more than 1 damage to a targeted hero, you discard 1 card of each suit and lose 3 health.
(You must discard as many different suits as you are able to.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Cao Cao</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>God</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: A Hero that Transcends the World

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Homage:
Whenever you are dealt damage, for each damage recieved, you may randomly take a card from each hero. Then flip your hero.
(You are allowed to take cards from their hand, judgement zone, or equipment zone of a hero. You name the area you want to take a card from and a card is randomly selected from that area.)

Flying Shadow:
The physical range other heroes see you is increased by +1.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Lu Bu</cardName>
      <portraitOverride>Lu Bu01</portraitOverride>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>God</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Way of the Asura

Health/Gender: 5M

Ability:

Violent Rage:
At the beginning of the game, you gain 2 [RAGE] tokens.
Whenever you deal or is dealt damage, you gain 1 [RAGE] token.

Simpleton:
Whenever you play a non-delay tactics card, choose one:
1. You discard 1 [RAGE] token.
2. You lose 1 health.

Unprecedented:
During your main phase, you may removed 2 [RAGE] tokens and choose a target hero, you ignore the effects of any armor equipped by the targeted hero and gain [MATCHLESS] until the end of turn.

Asura's Fury:
Once during your main phase, you may removed 6 [RAGE] tokens, then all other heroes are dealt 1 damage, discard all equipments, and discard 4 cards from their hand.
Then flip your hero card.

[Matchless]:
Whenever you are the source of an ATTACK, the defending hero needs to play 2 DODGE cards in order to cancel the ATTACK.
Whenever you are involved in a duel, the other hero needs to discard 2 ATTACK cards in order to respond to your discarded ATTACK.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Lu Bu</cardName>
      <portraitOverride>Lu Bu02</portraitOverride>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>God</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Myth of the Formidable

Health/Gender: 8M

Ability:

Horsemanship:
The physical range you see other heroes is reduced by 1.

Matchless:
Whenever you are the source of an ATTACK, the defending hero needs to play 2 DODGE cards in order to cancel the ATTACK.
Whenever you are involved in a duel, the other hero needs to discard 2 ATTACK cards in order to respond to your discarded ATTACK.

Special Notes:

Turn Priority:
Lu Bu, Myth of the Formidable does not follow the normal turn order, the turn order still is taken in counter-clockwise direction, but whenever another hero ends their turn, Lu Bu, Myth of the Formidable then takes a turn.

Form Transition: 
Whenever the deck is depleted or your health reaches 4 units or lower, the current hero taking their turn immediately ends.
Then you choose to transform into one of these forms:
1.Lu Bu, Rage of the God of War
2.Lu Bu, War Spirit without Precedent

If the transformation was due to the deck depleteing, your max health is set to your current health amount.
If the transformation was due to your health decreasing, you max health becomes 4 units and you are at full health.

Then remove all cards from judgement and equipment zone; and begin your turn immediately.
(If this was triggered durring turn, your current turn ends immediately after meeting the conditions; then continue resolving the rest of the effect.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Lu Bu</cardName>
      <portraitOverride>Lu Bu03</portraitOverride>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>God</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Rage of the God of War

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Horsemanship:
The physical range you see other heroes is reduced by 1.

Matchless:
Whenever you are the source of an ATTACK, the defending hero needs to play 2 DODGE cards in order to cancel the ATTACK.
Whenever you are involved in a duel, the other hero needs to discard 2 ATTACK cards in order to respond to your discarded ATTACK.

Asura:
At the beginning of your turn, you may discard a card sharing the same suit as a delay tactics card in your judgement zone to discard the delay tactics card.

Divine Might:
You draw 3 additional cards during you draw phase.
You hand size limit is increased by 3.

Divine Halberd:
If you do not have a weapon equipped, you may target 2 additional heroes with your ATTACKs, you may also play an additional ATTACK during your turn.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Lu Bu</cardName>
      <portraitOverride>Lu Bu04</portraitOverride>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>God</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: War Spirit without Precedent

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Matchless:
Whenever you are the source of an ATTACK, the defending hero needs to play 2 DODGE cards in order to cancel the ATTACK.
Whenever you are involved in a duel, the other hero needs to discard 2 ATTACK cards in order to respond to your discarded ATTACK.

Divine Vessel:
At the beginning of each hero's turn, if the cards in your hand is equal to your max health or less, you may draw 2 cards.
Whenever you are dealt damage, you may use a Peach.

Martial Prowess:
During your main phase, you may discard a card from your hand and gain a following ability until the end of turn:
1. [ASSAULT]
2. [FIRECE EDGE]
3. [WHIRLWIND]
4. [PERFECT MURDER]

[Assault]:
Once during your main phase, you may lose 1 health or discard an equipment card; If you do, you deal 1 damage to a target hero.

[Fierce Edge]:
Whenever you deal damage to a target hero, you may clash with that hero. If you win, you may take 1 card from that hero's hand or equipment zone into your hand.

[Whirlwind]:
Whenever you discard at least 2 cards during your discard phase; or you lose a card in your equipment zone, you may choose up to 2 target heroes and discard up to 2 cards from their hand or equipment zone.

[Perfect Murder]:
During your turn, if a hero is on the brink of death; only you and that hero may use PEACH cards.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
  </CardData>
</CardDataCollection>