<?xml version="1.0" encoding="Windows-1252"?>
<CardDataCollection xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <CardData>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Sun Quan</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Young and Worthy Lord

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Balance of Power:
Once during your main phase, you may discard any number of cards from your hand and equipment zone; then draw that same amount of cards.

Rescued: (Emperor Ability)
Whenever you are on the brink of death and a WU faction hero uses a PEACH on you, you gain 2 health instead of 1.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Sun Ce</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Young Conqueror of Jiangdong

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Ardor:
Whenever you target a hero with a DUEL or RED ATTACK (vice versa), you may draw a card.

Soul Aura: (Awakening Ability)
At the beginning of your turtn, if you have exactly 1 health, reduce your maximum health by 1 unit, then gain the [DASHING HERO] and [BRAVE SPIRIT] abilities. Your hand size limit is now equal to the amount of your maximum health.

Hegemony: (Emperor Ability)
Once during each other WU faction hero's main phase, that hero may choose to clash with you. If that hero did not win, you can take the 2 cards reveal for the clash into your hand.
If you have triggered [SOUL AURA], you may refuse these clashes.

[Dashing Hero]:
During your drawing phase, draw an additional card.
You hand size limit is your max health instead of you current health.

[Brave Sprit]:
At the beginning of your turn, if you are damaged, you may have another target hero choose one of the following:
1. Target hero draws X cards, then discards 1 card from their hand or equipment zone.
2. Target hero raws 1 card, then discards X cards from their hand or equipment zone.
(X is your missing health.)</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Sun Xiu</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Emperor Who Tries to Save the Country

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Hostile Banquet:
Once during your main phase, you may choose another target hero to choose one of the following:
1. The targeted hero discards a card.
2. The targeted hero gives you all the equipment cards from their equipment zone, then you lose the [HOSTILE BANQUET] ability for the rest of the game, and then upgrade [VITALIZING EDUCATION].
(The equipment cards given to you are put into your hand.)

Vitalizing Education:
At the end of your turn, you may target X heroes. Each target hero in sequence draws a card and then puts a card on top of the library from their hand or equipment zone.
(X is your current health.)

(Upgrade):
At the end of your turn, you may target X heroes. Each target hero in sequence draws a card and then puts a card on top of the library from their hand or equipment zone.
(X is your max health.)

Bound by orders: (Emperor Ability)
Heroes within your physical range are treated as within the attack range of other WU faction heroes.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Sun Hao</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Last Emperor of Wu

Health/Gender: 5M

Ability:

Ruin:
You may skip your draw phase and draw X cards. Until the end of your turn, whenever you play a basic or tactics card, you must discard a card.
(X is the number of heroes with missing health.)

Hatred:
Whenever you are dealt damage, if you do not have any cards in your hand, the dealt damage is increased by +1.

Return to Life: (Emperor Ability)
During your turn, other WU faction heroes are considered to have missing health, regardless of the amount of their current health.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Sun Liang</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Prince of Kuaji

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Execute:
At the end of your discard phase, you may choose one:
1. Choose X target heroes to draw a card in turn sequence.
2. Deal 1 damage to any number of heroes with current health equal to X.
(X is the number of cards you have discarded during your discard phase.)

Hinder:
During your main phase, you cannot target heroes that do not have you within their attack range.
At the end of your main phase, if the number of cards you played is less than the number of target heroes that do not have you within their attack range, you discard a card from each of those hero's hand or equipment zones.

Army Establishment: (Emperor Ability)
Whenever another WU faction hero plays an ATTACK during thier main phase, after the ATTACK is resolved; that hero may give the ATTACK to you, then you may have that hero draw a card.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Gan Ning</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Pirate with Silk Sails

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Surprise Raid:
During your main phase, you may play any BLACK cards in your hand and equipment zone as a BURN BRIDGES.

Prestige: (Limited ability)
Once per game, whenever a tactics card targets 2 or more heroes, you may have any number of targeted heroes ignore the effects of the card.
(The card being played still counts as targeting the heroes. When resolving HARVEST, the cards are revealed before you choose to remove any targeted heroes.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Lu Meng</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Crossing the River in White Robes

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Self-Restraint:
If you did not play or discard any ATTACK during your main phase, you may skip your discard phase.

Diligence: (Awakening Ability)
At the beginning of your turn, if the number of cards in your hand is greater than X+3, reduce your max health by 1 unit and gain the [STRIKE AT THE HEART] ability.
(X is you current health. If the game started with 7 or more heroes, X is 2.)

[Strike at the Heart]:
Once during your main phase, you may choose another target hero and look at the cards in their hand, then reveal a HEARTS suited card and choose one:
1. Discard the HEARTS suited card.
2. Place the card on top of the deck.
(When resolving this ability with Xiao Qiao, any SPADES suited cards can be selected as HEARTS suited card due to her [YOUTHFUL BEAUTY] ability.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Huang Gai</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Sacrificing for the Country

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Sacrificial Injury:
Once during your main phase, you may discard a card; then you lose 1 life.

False Surrender:
Whenever you lose 1 health, draw 3 cards.
Whenever you lose health during your main phase, you may play an additional ATTACK this turn; until the end of your turn, RED ATTACKs you play ignore all range requirements and cannot be canceled by a DODGE.
(This ability does not activate when you are dealt damage, only when damage recieved is counted as loss of health.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhou Yu</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Wu Viceroy

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Dashing Hero:
During your drawing phase, draw an additional card.
You hand size limit is your max health instead of you current health.

Sow Discord:
Once during your main phase, you may reveal a card from your hand and give it to another target hero. Then that hero chooses one:
1. Targeted hero reveals the cards in their hand and discards all cards with the same suit as the card you revealed.
2. Targeted hero loses 1 health.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Da Qiao</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Reserved Beauty

Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

National Beauty:
During your main phase, you may play DIAMONDS suited cards as ACEDIA or discard a DIAMONDS suited card to discard a ACEDIA from a hero's judgement zone; then draw a card.

Displacement:
Whenever you are the target of an ATTACK, you may discard a card from your hand or equipment zone; then choose another target hero other the attacker within your attack range, that hero becomes the new target of the ATTACK.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Lu Xun</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Meek Scholar with Valiant Talents

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Humility:
Whenever your are the only target of a tactics card or when a delay tactics card effect targets you, you may attach all cards in your hand onto your hero face down.
At the end of the turn, you take the attached cards back itno your hand.

One After Another:
Whenever you have no more cards in your hand, you may choose X heros to draw a card.
(X is the number of cards you had before having no cards left in your hand.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Sun Shang Xiang</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Archery Princess

Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Marriage:
Once During your main phase, you may discard 2 cards and choose a target MALE hero; if you do, you and that hero gain 1 health.

Warrior Princess:
Whenever a card is removed from your equipment zone, draw 2 cards.
(Removed meaning that your card will no longer be in your equipment zone. Replacing your own equipment will activate this ability.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Xiao Qiao</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Unconventional Beauty

Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Heavenly Scent:
Whenever you are being dealt damage, you may discard a HEARTS suited card from your hand to prevent the damage; then choose another target hero and choose one of the following:
1. Have the source of damage deal 1 damage to the targeted hero, then that hero draws X cards. (X is the targeted hero's missing health. Max of 5 cards.)
2. Have the targeted hero lose 1 health, then the targeted hero takes the card you discarded to activate [HEAVENLY SCENT].

(You are not suppose to suffer any damage when performing this ability. You do not become the new source of damage, the original source of damage does not change when activatign this ability. The hero must be saved from the brink of death in order to be able to draw or take cards. When you you transfer incomming damage from a chained source, you do not become unchained after doing so since you do not take any elemental damage.)

Youthful Beauty:
Your SPADES suited cards in your hand, equipment zone, and any judgement card results are considered to be HEARTS suited cards instead.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhou Tai</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Battle Records in Scars

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Undying:
Whenever you are on the brink of death, reveal a card from the top of the library; then if there are no [WOUND] cards with same rank attached to you, you return 1 health and attach the revealed card as a [WOUND] card onto your hero. If there is a [WOUND] card with the same rank as your revealed card, discard the revealed card into the graveyard and return to resolving your brink of death phase.
If you have any [WOUND] cards attached to your hero, your hand size limit becomes equal to the number of [WOUND] cards attached to your hero.
(You must activate this ability before being able to ask other players to play a PEACH for you.)

Inspire:
Whenever a hero has a card from their hand discarded or taken by another hero, you may lose 1 life. If you do, the hero that lost cards draws 2 cards.
(You cannot activate this ability in response to a hero discarding cards from their own ability, but you can when a targeted hero is forced to discard due to another hero's ability. You may activate this ability per instance, even though a hero may be discarding more than 1 card at a time. You are allowed to target yourself with this ability as well.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Tai Shi Ci</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Ardent and Loyal Warrior

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Righteousness:
Once during your main phase, you may clash with another target hero. If you win, you may play an additional ATTACK this turn; until the end of your turn, your ATTACKs may target an additional hero and ignore all range requirements.
If you did not win, you cannot play ATTACK cards until the end of your turn.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Sun Jiang</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Martial Emperor of Unyielding

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Brave Sprit:
At the beginning of your turn, if you are damaged, you may targeted another hero and choose one of the following:
1. The targeted hero draws X cards, then discards 1 card from their hand or equipment zone.
2. The targeted hero draws 1 card, then discards X cards from their hand or equipment zone.
(X is your missing health.)</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Lu Su</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Maverick Diplomat

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Altruism:
During your drawing phase, you may draw 2 additional cards; then if the number of cards in your hand is greater than 5, give half of the cards (rounded down) to another target hero with the least number of cards in their hand.

Alliance:
Once during your main phase, you may choose 2 target heroes and discard X cards from you hand or equipment zone (X is the difference between the number of cards in both targeted hero's hand). If you do, those heros exchange the cards in their hand.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhang Zhao &amp; Zhang Hong</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Genius Prime Ministers

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Blunt Advice:
During your main phase, you may play an equipment card onto another hero's equipment zone, then draw 1 card.
(You cannot replace a equipment from an occupied slot.)

Solid Governance:
At the end of each other hero's discard phase, you may put 1 card discarded by that hero during their discard phase back into their hand, then take all other discarded cards into your hand.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Ling Tong</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Forthright and Courageous

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Whirlwind:
Whenever you discard at least 2 cards during your discard phase; or you lose a card in your equipment zone, you may choose up to 2 target heroes and discard up to 2 cards from their hand or equipment zone.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Wu Guo Tai</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Martial Empress of Unyielding

Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Amrita:
Once during your main phase, you may choose 2 target heroes with equipment in their equipment zone, if the difference between the number of equipments is less than or equal to X, exchange their equipment.
(X is your missing health)

Ameliorate:
When a hero is on the brink of death, you may reveal a card from that hero's hand, if the revealed card is a non-basic card, discard it and that hero gains 1 health.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Xu Shen</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Steel Barricade of Jiang Dong

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Breakthrough:
Whenever you play an ATTACK targeting a hero, you may take X cards from his hand or equipment zone and set them aside facing down. (X is his current health) Return those cards to that hero's hand at the end of your turn.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Bu Lianshi</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Uncrowned Queen

Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Pacify:
Once during your main phase, you may choose 2 target heroes with different amounts of cards in their hand, the hero with the least amount cards in their hand takes a card from the hero with the higher amount of cards in their hand and then reveals it. If the suit of the revealed card is not a SPADES suit, you draw a card.

Reminiscence:
When you are dead, you may choose a target hero other than the killer, that hero draws 3 cards and gains 1 health.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Cheng Pu</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Loyalist of Three Generations

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Plague Fire:
Whenever you play an ATTACK, you may treat it as a FIRE ATTACK. If this FIRE ATTACK deals damage, you lose 1 health.
This FIRE ATTACK may target an additional hero.

Superior Vintage:
At the end of your turn, if you have no [VINTAGE] cards attached to your hero card, you may attach any number of ATTACK cards onto your hero as [VINTAGE]. Whenever a hero is on the brink of death, you may discard a [VINTAGE] card; this is treated as that hero playing a WINE.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Han Dang</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Marquis of the Stone City

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Mounted Archer:
Once during your main phase, you may discard a card from your hand or equipment zone; if you do, ignore attack range requirements until the end of your turn. If the discarded card is an equipment card, you may discard a card from another target hero's hand or equipment zone.

Problem Solve: (Limited Ability)
During your main phase, you may choose a target hero. All heroes that that have the targeted hero within their attack range must choose to:
1. Discard a weapon card.
2. Allow the targeted hero to draw a card.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Pan Zhang &amp; Ma Zhong</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Nightmare of Ace

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Seize Weapon:
Whenever you are dealt damage by an ATTACK, you may discard a card from your hand or equipment zone. If you do, take the weapon from the equipment zone of the source of damage into your hand.

Backstab:
Whenever you have dealt damage to a target hero with an ATTACK, if you are not within his attack range, this ATTACK deals an 1 additional damage.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Yu Fan</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Unrestrained and Honest Advisor

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Seek Knowledge:
Whenever you discard your cards, you may put any number of them on top of the library.

Blunt Words:
At the end of your turn, you may target a hero. That hero draws a card and reveals it. If that card is an equipment card, that hero must play that equipment card and then gain 1 health.
(The equipment card replaces any previous equipment that shared the same slot.)</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhu Ran</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Patient Commander

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Courage:
During your main phase, you may discard X cards and choose another target hero within your attack range.
(X is the number of times you activate [COURAGE] during this turn, the first time you activate [COURAGE] is treated as 1.)
If X is:
1:  You discard a card from target hero's hand, equipment or judgment zone.
2:  Target hero gives you a card from their hand, equipment or judgment zone.
3:  You deal 1 damage to target hero.
4+: You and target hero draw 2 cards.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Sun Lu Ban</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Henchwoman

Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Slander:
Once during your main phase, whenever you play an ATTACK or BLACK non-delay tactics card targeting a single hero, you may choose a second hero who may also be targeted by your card. The second targeted hero chooses one of the following:
1. The second targeted hero gives you a card and becomes the source for the card you have played.
2. The second targeted also becomes the additional target to the card you have played.
(If the source of the ATTACK changes from you, you are still considered to have played an ATTACK this turn and cannot play another ATTACK due to the ATTACK restriction limit.)

Arrogant:
Whenever you are dealt damage by a MALE hero, you may discard an equipment card and reduce that damage by 1.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhu Huan</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Defender of Chung Chou

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Hard Work:
If you are the hero with the highest number of cards in your hand, you may skip your draw phase.
If you are the hero with the highest amount of current health, you may skip your main phase.
If you are the hero with the highest number of equipments in your equipment zone, you may skip your discard phase.

Suppressing Bandits:
At the end of your turn, you may deal 1 damage to up to X target heroes.
(X is the number of phases you have skipped this turn. You cannot do multiple damage to the same hero.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Gu Yong</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Wu's Prime Minister

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Prudent:
During your main phase, you may discard 2 cards from your hand or equipment zone. If you do, draw a card.

In the Same Spirit:
At the end of your turn, you may reveal your hand. If all the revealed cards are the same color, you may choose X heroes to draw a card. (X is the number of cards in your hand.)</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhu Zhi</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: General of National Stability

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Secure Nation:
Once during your main phase, you may choose a target hero. If the targeted hero:
1. Has the lowest amount of cards in their hand, they draw a card.
2. Has the lowest health, they gain 1 health.
3. Has the lowest amount of equipped equipments, they randomly equip a equipment card from the library.

If the targeted hero does not match with any of the requirements, but you match them; you gain the effects from this abilitiy instead.
(The equipment that the targeted hero equips will replace any equipment that already occupies a equipment zone.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Quan Cong</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Greedy Noble

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Seeking Fame:
Once during each hero's turn, whenever you have dealt or was dealt damage, you may choose one of the following:
1. Discard a card from target hero's hand. That hero must have more cards in their hand than you.
2. Target hero draws a card. That hero must have less cards in hand than you.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Sun Deng</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Talented and Virtuous Crowned Prince

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Rectify:
Once during your main phase, you may target another hero. That hero may attach up to 3 cards (At least 1.) from his hand or equipment zone onto your hero face down as [RECTIFICATION] cards. If he does, at the beginning of your next turn, you take all [RECTIFICATION] cards attached to you into your hand and the target hero draws the amount of [RECTIFICATON] cards you have recieved.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Cen Hun</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Eunuch Who Ordered National Isolation

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Extravagant:
During your main phase, if your hand limit is greater than 0, you may draw a card then reduce your hand limit by 1 until the end of your turn. At the end of your turn, if you have no cards in your hand, you may choose up to X target heros to be chained.
(X is your current health)

Chain of Disasters:
Whenever you are dealt FIRE damage, if your hero card is chained and you are the first hero among the chained heroes to receive the damage, this damage is increased by +1.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Xu Shi</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Beautiful Empress of Justice

Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Ask for Divinatory Diagram:
Once during each hero's main phase, the active hero may give you a card and you decide to place it on top or bottom of the library. If you do, both you and the active hero draws a card from the opposite side of the library.
(If the active hero is you, you do not have to reveal the card and you are only allowed to draw 1 card.)

Execution:
At the end of a MALE hero's turn, if the remaining number of cards in the library is less than or equal to X (X is your current health x 10), then you can play all ATTACK cards from the library on that MALE hero ignoring any range requirements, then shuffle the library.
(The number of ATTACK cards that can be played cannot exceed the number of surviving heroes)</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zong Xue</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Elegantly Simple Minister

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Recovery:
When another target hero plays a card in response to a card you have played, you may give the card you played to that hero and take the card that hero played into your hand. (That hero cannot play the given card this turn.)

(Upgrade):
When another target hero plays a card in response to a card you have played, you may take the card that hero played into your hand.

Training:
At the end of your turn, you may have target hero draw as many cards as there are DIAMONDS suited cards on the field. Then that hero discards X cards. If they have discarded all their cards, you can upgrade [RECOVERY] and lose the [TRAINING] ability for the rest of the game.
(X is the number of times you activated this skill during this game.)</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Sun Yang</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Chasing the Waves and Wind

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Torpedo:
You draw 1+X aditional cards during your draw phase.
(X is half the number of equipment cards in your equipment zone rounded down.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Ye Shi Wen</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Ascending Green Lotus

Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Afterimage:
At the beginning of your turn, you may skip your judgement and draw phase to target another hero, treat this as playing an ATTACK on the targeted hero, ignore any range requirements for these ATTACK.

Release:
Ignore the effects of all sources of FIRE damage.
(You are immune to all sources of FIRE damage, including incomming FIRE damage from being in the chained state and redirected damage from Xiao Qiao.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Da Qiao &amp; Xiao Qiao</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Flowers of Jiandong

Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Star Dance:
At the beginning of your discard phase, you may attach a card from your hand face up onto your characeter as a [STEP]. The card you attach must be a different color than the cards you have used this turn. Whenever you have 3 [STEPS] attached, remove them all and choose a target MALE hero, you deal 2 damage to the target hero and discard all equiped epuipment cards.
(If you used both RED and BLACK cards this turn, you cannot attach any [STEPS] onto yourself. If you did not play any cards on your turn, you will not be allowed to attach any [STEP] cards. If you reach 3 [STEPS] and there are no MALE heroes, you must still remove all the [STEPS] while  not being able to deal damage or discarding equipment cards.)

River Swans:
Whenever you have [STEP] cards attached, you may use the [DISPLACEMENT] and [HEAVENLY SCENT] abilities.

[Displacement]:
Whenever you are the target of an ATTACK, you may discard a card from your hand or equipment zone; then choose another target hero other the attacker within your attack range, that hero becomes the new target of the ATTACK.

[Heavenly Scent]:
Whenever you are being dealt damage, you may discard a HEARTS suited card from your hand to prevent the damage; then choose another target hero and choose one of the following:
1. Have the source of damage deal 1 damage to the targeted hero, then that hero draws X cards. (X is the targeted hero's missing health. Max of 5 cards.)
2. Have the targeted hero lose 1 health, then the targeted hero takes the card you discarded to activate [HEAVENLY SCENT].

(You are not suppose to suffer any damage when performing this ability. You do not become the new source of damage, the original source of damage does not change when activatign this ability. The hero must be saved from the brink of death in order to be able to draw or take cards. When you you transfer incomming damage from a chained source, you do not become unchained after doing so since you do not take any elemental damage.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhuge Jin</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Preserver of the Alliance

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Aid:
During your draw phase, you may draw 1 less card; then choose up to 2 other target heroes to draw a card.

Delayed Release:
Whenever a hero performs a judgment, before revealing the result, you may have that hero look at the cards in your hand and choose one to be the judgement result.

Shrewdness:
Whenever you play or discard RED cards outside of your turn, you may draw a card.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhuge Ke</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Thinking of Family Back Home

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Arrogance:
Whenever you need to play a basic card outside of your turn, you may look at the top 2 cards of the library. If the card you need to play is present, you may use it immediately.
(Any cards you do not use are placed ontop of the library in the same order once your ability has resolved.)

Recklessness:
During your main phase, you may choose to target a hero within your attack range and discard X cards; then you deal 1 damage to that hero. If you bring the targeted hero to the brink of death in this way, you lose 1 health and cannot use this ability for the rest of the turn.
(X is the current health of the target hero.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Sun Lu Yu</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Small Tiger

Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Charm:
At the beginning of another hero's main phase, you may have target hero gain the [CEASE] ability until the end of your turn. If you do, you are considered to be within the targeted hero's attack range.

(Upgrade):
At the beginning of another hero's main phase, you may have target hero gain the [CEASE] ability until the end of your turn.

Solemn:
Once during a hero's main phase, you may discard a card and choose one:
1. Discard a equipment from a targeted hero's equipment zone; then draw a card.
2. Take an armor from a targeted hero's equipment zone.
If the card you discarded to activate [SOLEMN] was an ATTACK or a BLACK tactics card, upgrade [CHARM] until the beginning of your next turn.

[Cease]:
After you play a tactics card, your tactics cards are treated as ATTACKs until the end of turn.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Ding Feng</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Essential Minister who Purged the King's Court

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Short Soldiers:
Your ATTACKs may target an additional hero within your physical range.

Swift and Deadly:
Once during each hero's main phase, you may discard a card and target another hero, the physical range between you and the targeted hero is 1 until the end of turn.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zu Mao</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Scarlet Bloodstained Conical Cap

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Leading the Troops:
At the end of your turn, you may attach any number of non-basic cards face up onto your hero as a [VANGUARD]. Whenever you are dealt damage by an ATTACK or DUEL, remove a [VANGUARD].
(You may choose which [VANGUARD] card to be removed from yourself.)

Danger Zone:
At the beginning of your turn, you choose one:
1. Remove all [VANGUARD] cards and draw cards until you have X cards in your hand. (X is your max health.)
2. Give all [VANGUARD] cards to another target hero whose health is not greater than your current health; then the target hero gains 1 health and you draw X cards. (X is the number of [VANGUARD] cards given to the targeted hero.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Bu Zhi</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Integrating Solutions in Jiangbian

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Kindness:
Whenever you gain or lose 2 or more cards from a source, you may have a another target hero draw a card.

Settle Rebellion:
During your main phase, you may activate [SETTLE REBELLION] X times; you may have a target hero with an equipment in their equipment zone draw a card, then the targeted hero chooses one:
1. You discard an equipment from the targeted hero.
2. The targeted hero takes all equipment cards in their equipment zones back into their hand and deal 1 damage to you.
(X is the number of surviving rebels in the game.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Han Ze</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Truly Insightful Adviser

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Alight the Letter:
At the beginning of your main phase, you may give all the cards in your hand to another hero, then that hero reveals any number of cards from their hand and you choose one:
1. Take the cards that were revealed.
2. Take the cards that were not revealed.

Wide Release:
At the end of your turn, you may choose a target hero in secret. Until the beginning of your next turn, whenever the targeted hero is dealt more than 1 damage by a source; prevent that damage, then skip your draw phase on your next turn.
(The hero that you choose to be the target of [WIDE RELEASE[ is only known to you. The additional FIRE damage effect from RATTAN ARMOR is calculated after this ability activates, so the targeted hero will still take 1 FIRE damage.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>He Qi</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Leading Calvalry through the Mountains

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Damask Helmet:
You gain the following abilities based on the number of different suits in your equipment zone:
1: [HORSEMANSHIP]
2: [DASHING HERO]
3: [SHORT SOLDIER]
4: [PRESTIGE]

Quick Raid:
Once during your main phase, you may discard a RED basic card to discard a card from a target hero within your attack range. If the discarded card is a DODGE, you look at the cards in the targeted hero's hand. If the discarded card is not a DODGE, the targeted hero looks at the card in your hand.

[Horsemanship]:
The physical range you see other heroes is reduced by 1.

[Dashing Hero]:
During your drawing phase, draw an additional card.
You hand size limit is your max health instead of you current health.

[Short Soldiers]:
Your ATTACKs may target an additional hero within your physical range of you.

[Prestige]: (Limited ability)
Once per game, whenever a tactics card targets 2 or more heroes, you may have any number of targeted heroes ignore the effects of the card.
(The card being played still counts as targeting the heroes. When resolving HARVEST, the cards are revealed before you choose to remove any targeted heroes.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Liu Zan</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Echoing Ferocious Warcry

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Warcry:
During your turn, whenever you play a card with a color different from your previous card, you may draw a card.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Ling Cao</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Rushing Torrent

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Advance Forward:
You draw 1+X aditional cards during your draw phase.
(X is half the number of equipment cards in your equipment zone rounded down.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Sun Ru</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Ascending Green Lotus

Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Swim:
Ignore the effects of all sources of FIRE damage.
(You are immune to all sources of FIRE damage, including incomming FIRE damage from being in the chained state and redirected damage from Xiao Qiao.)

Sprint:
At the beginning of your turn, you may skip your judgement and draw phase to target another hero, treat this as playing an ATTACK on the targeted hero, ignore any range requirements for these ATTACK.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Lu Ji</cardName>
      <portraitOverride />
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Green</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Scholar with Promising Talent

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Keeping Oranges:
At the beginning of the game you gain 3 [ORANGE] tokens attached to your hero.

Discourtesy:
At the beginning of your main phase, you may lose 1 health or remove an [ORANGE] token to have a target hero gain a [ORANGE] token.

Organizing Theories:
At the beginning of your drawing phase, if you have no [ORANGE] tokens attached, you may skip your draw phase and gain a [ORANGE] token.

[Orange]:
During the drawing phase, if a hero has an an [ORANGE] token attached, that hero draws an extra card.
Whenever a hero with an attached [ORANGE] is dealt damage, prevent that damage and remove an [ORANGE] token.
(You only draw 1 extra card, you do not draw a card per each [ORANGE] token attached to your hero. Whenever you are dealt damage with an [ORANGE] token attached, you must discard it when resolving to take the damage.)
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
  </CardData>
</CardDataCollection>