<?xml version="1.0" encoding="Windows-1252"?>
<CardDataCollection xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <CardData>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Liu Bei</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Hero Through Troubled Times

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Kindness:
During your main phase, you may give any number of cards in your hand to any number of heroes, the first time you give out 2 or more cards to a hero, you gain 1 Health.

Rouse: (Emperor Ability)
Whenever you need to play or discard an ATTACK, any other Shu heroes can play or discard for you.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Liu Shan</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Emperor with No Achievements

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Relish: (Passive)
Whenever you become the target of an ATTACK, ignore the effects of that ATTACK unless the attacker discards a basic card from their hand.

Devolution:
You may skip your main phase, then at the end of your turn, you may discard a card and target a hero. That hero immediately gains an extra turn.

Eiron: (Awakening Ability, Emperor Ability)
At the beginning of your turn, if you have the least amount of health among all heroes, you increase your max health by 1 unit, gain 1 health, and gain [ROUSE].

[ROUSE]:
Whenever you need to play or discard an ATTACK, any other Shu hero may play or discard one for you.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Liu Zhang</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Patriotic Noble

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Do or Die:
During your main phase, you may discard all cards in your hand and treat this as playing DUEL, after resolving the duel, you and the loser of the duel draw a card. If you drew 2 or more cards via this effect during this phase, you loose [DO OR DIE] until the end of turn.

Save the Emperor: (Emperor ability)
You may discard a card to use [ROUSE]. the hero who used an ATTACK to respond to your [ROUSE] draws a card.

[ROUSE]:
Whenever you need to play or discard an ATTACK, any other Shu heroes can play or discard for you.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Guan Yu</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Bearded Gentleman

Health/Gender:4M

Ability:

Saint Warrior:
You may play or use any RED cards from your hand or equipment zone as ATTACK.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhang Fei</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: A Match for Ten Thousand Warriors

Health/Gender:4M

Ability:

Roar:
You may play any number of ATTACK during your turn.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhuge Liang</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Prime Minister Who Has Passed His Prime

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Stargazing:
At the beginning of the turn, you may look at the top X cards of your library, where X is equal to the number of surviving heroes (Max 5), you may choose to put any number of these cards on top of the library and bottom of the library in any order.

Empty Fort: (Passive)
When you have no cards in your hand, you cannot be the target of ATTACK or DUEL.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhao Yun</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Young General

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Dragon Courage:
You may play or use ATTACK cards as DODGE or vice versa.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Ma Chao</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Lone Horseman That Can Outmatch a Thousand Troops

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Horsemanship:
Your range with other heroes is always reduced by 1.

Iron Calvary:
Whenever you play an ATTACK on a hero, you may perform a judgment. If the result is RED, the ATTACK cannot be responded by DODGE.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Huang Yue Ying</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Veiled Heroine

Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Gathering Wisdom:
Whenever you play an non-delay tactics card, draw a card.

Wondrous Talent:
Ignore range requirements when you play a tactics card.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Huang Zhong</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Old But Strong

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Fearsome Archer:
When you use an ATTACK, you may target a hero whose range between you and him is less than the rank of that ATTACK.

Whenever you target a hero with an ATTACK:
1. If the number of cards in his hand is less than or equal to yours, this ATTACK cannot be cancelled by DODGE.
2. If his current health is greater than or equal to your health, this ATTACK damage is +1.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Wei Yan</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Bloodthirsty Lone Wolf

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Violent Spirit:
Whenever you have dealt damage to a player within your range, for each damage you have dealt, you choose one:
1. Gain 1 Health.
2. Draw 1 card.

Surprise Tactics: (Limited Ability)
During your main phase, you may lose X life, then until the end of your turn, you may use additional X ATTACK cards and your range with other heroes are reduced by X.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Young Zhuge Liang</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Sleeping Dragon

Health/Gender: 3M

Eight Trigrams: (Passive)
If you have no armor card in your equipment zone, you are considered to have [EIGHT TRIGRAMS] equipped.

Arson:
During your main phase, you may play RED cards in your hand as BLAZE.

See Through:
You may play BLACK cards in your hand as IMPECCABLE PLAN.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhu Rong</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Queen of Wilds

Health/Gender: 4F

Ability:

Elephant Army: (Passive)
You are immune to BARBARIAN ASSAULT. Whenever a BARBARIAN ASSAULT is played by another hero, after it is resolved and put into graveyard, take the card into your hand.

Fierce Edge:
Whenever you have dealt damage to a target hero, you may clash with him. If you win, you may take 1 card from his hand or equipment zone into your hand.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Meng Huo</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: King of Southern Barbarians
	  
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Culprit: (Passive)
You are immune to BARBARIAN ASSAULT. You are the source of any BARBARIAN ASSAULT.

Resurgence:
During your draw phase, if you are damaged, you may skip your draw phase and reveal X card from the deck. 
(X is equal to the amount of health you lost)

For each HEART card revealed, discard it and you gain 1 health then put the remaining revealed cards into your hand.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Jiang Wei</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Dragon's Successor

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Provoke:
Once per main phase, you may target a hero who can attack you, he must play an ATTACK on you. If he does not, you choose and discard 1 card from his hand, equipment zone, or judgment zone.

Recommence the Legacy: (Awakening Ability)
At the beginning of your turn, if you have no cards in your hand, gain 1 health or draw 2 cards, then reduce your max health by 1 and gain [STARGAZING].

[STARGAZING]:
At the beginning of the turn, you may look at the top X cards of your library, where X is equal to the number of surviving heroes (Max 5), you may choose to put any number of these cards on top and bottom of the library in any order.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Ma Su</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Arrogant Talent

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Talebearer:
Once per main phase, you may discard a card and choose a target hero with the highest health, then you deal 1 damage to them.
(If there several heroes with the highest health, you may choose one of them)

Subdue the Barbarians:
Whenever you have dealt damage to another hero, you may prevent that damage. If you do, take 1 card from that hero's equipment or judgment zone into your hand.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Fa Zheng</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Supporter of Shu

Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Reciprocation:
Whenever you gain 2 cards from another hero, you may have that hero draw a card. Whenever you are dealt damage, for each damage, the damage source chooses one of the following:
1. Give you a card from their hand.
2. Lose 1 health.

Dazzle:
During your drawing phase, you may skip your draw and target another hero to draw 2 cards, then that hero must play an ATTACK on another hero of your choice within their attack range. If that hero does not, take 2 cards from their hand.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Xu Shu</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Loyal Gallant

Health/Gender:3M

Ability:

Silence:
All damage from you deal or is dealt to you from tactics cards are prevented.

Recommendation:
At the end of your turn, you may discard a non-basic card from your hand or equipment zone to target another hero, that hero choose one of the following:
1. Draw 2 cards.
2. Gain 1 health.
3. Flip his hero card face up and untap it.

Note: Xu Shu is a Shu Hero, his card shares the Wei color because in history he was forced to join Cao Cao due to having his mother held hostage, but he did not give any advice to Cao Cao after he joined him as he was still loyal to Liu Bei.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Liao Hua</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Veteran Who Has Gone Through the Vicissitudes of Life

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Vanguard: (Passive)
At the beginning of your turn, you gain an extra main phase.

Aspirations: (Limited Ability)
When you are on the brink of death, you may gain X health.
(X is the number of factions in play)

If you do, flip your hero card.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Guan Xing &amp; Zhang Bao</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Cubs of the Generals

Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Paternal Souls:
During your main phase, you may use 2 cards in your hand as ATTACK. If this ATTACK deals damage, you gain [SAINT WARRIOR] and [ROAR] until the end of turn.

[SAINT WARRIOR]:
You may play or use any RED cards from your hand or equipment zone as ATTACK.

[ROAR]:
You may play any number of ATTACK during your turn.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Ma Dai</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Entrusted During Crisis
	  
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Horsemanship: (Passive)
Your range with other heroes is always reduced by 1.

Sneak Attack:
At the beggining of your turn, you may draw a card, then discard a card. If you do, you may target a hero within your range, the target hero cannot play or discard cards with the same color as your discarded card until the end of your turn.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Guan Ping</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Son of the Saint Warrior
	  
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Dragon Roar:
Whenever a hero play an ATTACK during their main phase, you may discard a card from hand or equipment zone. If you do, that ATTACK does not count towards the turn limit of ATTACK. If that ATTACK is RED, you draw a card.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Jian Yong</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Uninhibited Advisor
	  
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Fine Words:
At the beginning of your main phase, you may clash with another hero. If you win, the next basic or non-delay tactics card you use may target 1 additional or 1 less target. If you did not win, you cannot use tactics cards until the end of the turn.

Indulgence:
Whenever you win a clash, you may put the card with larger rank back to your hand, whenever you did not win a clash, you may put your clash card back to your hand.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Liu Feng</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Tragic Foster Son
	  
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Framed:
At the beginning of your turn, you may choose up to 2 target heroes. Put one card from each hero's hand or equipment zone onto your hero card as BETRAYAL. Whenever a player chooses to play an ATTACK on you, they may instead discard 2 BETRAYAL cards and this is treated as they playing an ATTACK towards you.
(This ATTACK counts towards the limited ATTACK rule.)</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Wu Yi</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Cavalry of Shu
	  
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Rapid Assault: (Passive)
Whenever you play a card during your turn, decrease your range with other heroes by 1. If your range with all other players is 1, you ignore another hero's armor and your ATTACK can target an additional hero.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhou Cang</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Shu Loyalist
	  
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Loyalty and Bravery:
After your ATTACK is resolved, you may give this ATTACK card or DODGE played by defending hero to another target hero. A hero who received a RED card through this may play an ATTACK to target hero within your attack range.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhang Song</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Waiting for a Worthy Emperor
	  
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Good memory:
At the start of your main phase, you may reveal a card from another hero's hand. Until the end of your turn, whenever you play a card with the same type as the revealed card, you draw a card.

Map offering:
At the start of other hero's main phases, you may draw 2 cards then give that hero 2 cards in your hand. At the end of the turn, if he did not kill any hero, you lose 1 health.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Xiahou Shi</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Whispering Beauty
	  
Health/Gender: 3F

Ability:

Gather Firewood:
At the end of each other hero's turn, if you and that hero have the same number of cards in hand, you may choose to let both of you draw a card.

Words of Swallow:
During your main phase, you may recast ATTACK cards. At the end of your main phase, if you've recasted 2 or more ATTACK cards, you may have target male hero draw 2 cards.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Zhang Ni</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Minority Soldier of Shu
	  
Health/Gender: 4M

Ability:

Pacifying Barbarians:
Once per main phase, you may choose a target hero. You and the target hero reveal a on-hand card at the same time. If you reveal an ATTACK and the target hero did not reveal a DODGE; you discard your ATTACK and deal 1 damage to the target hero. If you did not reveal an ATTACK and the target hero reveals a DODGE; you discard your revealed card and put a card from his hand or equipment zone into your hand.

Resolution: (Passive)
If your current health is 1, your DODGE are treated as ATTACK.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Li Yan</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Shu Rations Officer
	  
Health/Gender:3M

Ability:

Rations Management:
Once per main phase, you may put a card in another hero's hand into your hand, then you choose one of the following:
1. He look at the top 2 cards of the library, then reveal all basic cards and put them into his hand.
2. During his next draw phase, he draws an additional card.

Insidious: (Passive)
During your discard phase, cards you put into your hand this turn.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Huang Hao</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: The Trickery Eunuch
	  
Health/Gender:3M

Ability:

Emperor's Crony:
At the end of your turn, you may target a hero who has the Emperor within their attack range. You discard a card from that hero's hand or equipment zone, and then that hero draws a card. If that hero has more cards in their hand than the Emperor, you draw a card.

Bribery:
Once per a hero's turn, whenever you are dealt damage by another hero, you may reveal X cards in your hand and that hero chooses one of the following:
1. Target hero takes a revealed card and prevent the damage.
2. Target hero discards X cards from their hand or equipment zone.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Qin Zai</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Tongue that Pierces the Heavens
	  
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Admonish Attack:
When another hero uses an ATTACK on a target hero other than you, if you are within the attacker's attack range, you may place 1 hand card on top of the deck and cancel all the targets. If the ATTACK is not BLACK, you become the target instead.

Expert Opponent:
Whenever you play an ATTACK on target a hero, you may clash with the target hero. If you win, your ATTACK can't be cancelled by DODGE.
Whenever you become the target of an ATTACK you can clash with the attacker. If you win, the effects of the ATTACK is cancelled.

Heavenly Defense:
When you clash, you may use the top card of the library. The rank of your HEART suited cards are treated as a K rank.</cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Pang Tong</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Young Phoenix
      
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Shackles:
During you main phase, you may use a CLUB suited card in your hand as IRON CHAIN or recast that card.

Nirvana: (Limited Ability)
When you are on bRink of death, you may discard all cards in your hand, equipment zone and judgment zone, if you do, flip your hero card face up, draw 3 cards and gain 3 health.
      </cardDescription>
    </Card>
    <Card>
      <cardName>Wu Xian</cardName>
      <cardType>Heroes</cardType>
      <heroFaction>Red</heroFaction>
      <cardDescription>Title: Empress of Shu
	  
Health/Gender: 3M

Ability:

Good Fortune:
At the beginning of your turn, you may choose one:
1. You draw 1 additional card during your draw phase.
2. Once during this turn, your RED basic and non-delay tactics cards can target 1 additional player. (No range restrictions for the additional target)

If you have chosen a different option than your previous turn, add +1 to your chosen option's value for this turn, and then reset the values on this skill at the end of turn.

Careless
At the end of your turn you may have another target hero take 1 random HEART suited basic card from the deck. Then if that hero was the target of this skill in the previous turn, that hero loses 1 health.
</cardDescription>
    </Card>
  </CardData>
</CardDataCollection>